为什么所以我们离开了上一堂课，所以这是针对那些基于
why so we left the previous lecture so this is for those that was based on
this is for those that was based on lying this is the earlier lecture on
说谎，这是关于贝叶斯近似入门的较早讲授
lying this is the earlier lecture on introduction to approximate Bayesian
introduction to approximate Bayesian inference what's right was the other one
推断正确的是我让您忘记的另一个，好吧，我们找到了它
inference what's right was the other one I had you forgot okay we locate it so
I had you forgot okay we locate it so we're going to continue on that every
我们将继续在每个讲座中都有这个结冰的例子
we're going to continue on that every lecture there was this icing example
lecture there was this icing example that I went rapidly so let's review it
我走得很快，所以让我们回顾一下，因为这对于很多人来说非常重要
that I went rapidly so let's review it because it's very fundamental to lots of
because it's very fundamental to lots of areas all right so obviously you have
没事的地方，所以很明显，您已经在家庭作业中列出了清单
areas all right so obviously you have worked on lists in the homework we
worked on lists in the homework we assume here we have some observations
假设在这里我们有一些观察为什么，但是被定义为以像素为单位
assume here we have some observations why but are defined let's say pixel wise
why but are defined let's say pixel wise and X maybe the tradition image this is
X可能是传统图像，这是该图像的某些嘈杂版本，
and X maybe the tradition image this is some noisy version of the image and
some noisy version of the image and these are the original pictures we try
这些是我们尝试估计的原始图片，所以这里没有看到
these are the original pictures we try to estimate so there is no see here so
to estimate so there is no see here so you can think the unknowns basically are
您可以认为未知数基本上是X，这就是我们想要做的
you can think the unknowns basically are X this is what we want to do an
X this is what we want to do an inference and so we've worked with the
推论，所以我们使用了一些关节和后部
inference and so we've worked with the joint and the posterior with with some
joint and the posterior with with some prior the prior is basically standard
事前事前基本上是这类付款的标准是礼物
prior the prior is basically standard for this type of payments is is gift
for this type of payments is is gift like distribution e to the minus e0 some
例如将e分配到e0，则某些能量函数占
like distribution e to the minus e0 some energy functional that accounts for
energy functional that accounts for nearest neighbors basically interactions
最近的邻居基本上是互动的，好吧，这是非常典型的
nearest neighbors basically interactions okay this is sort of very typical of
okay this is sort of very typical of massaging models these are some
按摩模型这些是这里给出的一些系数兴奋的一天
massaging models these are some coefficients given here excited day
coefficients given here excited day they're binary variables plus minus one
它们是二进制变量再加上一减就可以了，所以我们喜欢这种可能性
they're binary variables plus minus one okay all right so we like the likelihood
okay all right so we like the likelihood locally is the product for all eyes on
在我为什么给定X的Y概率的情况下，本地产品是所有人的眼睛
locally is the product for all eyes on why I given the probability of Y given X
why I given the probability of Y given X I and we write this probability so we
我和我们写下这个概率，这样我们就可以
I and we write this probability so we can
can make the algebra to look nice has to get
要使代数看起来更好，就必须撒谎，所以总的来说
make the algebra to look nice has to get to the power a lie so the total
to the power a lie so the total likelihood basically is the exponential
可能性基本上是该能量单元I的总和的指数
likelihood basically is the exponential of the summation of this energy cell I
of the summation of this energy cell I of X I okay so that way we can write the
XI好的，这样我们就可以写出后验，就像在某些人的脑海中一样
of X I okay so that way we can write the posterior as if to the mind of some
posterior as if to the mind of some energy for the energies these little
为这些小矿工提供能量的地方证据的目的地
energy for the energies these little miners destination of the local evidence
miners destination of the local evidence which okay so what we want is we want to
好的，所以我们想要计算一个近似值
which okay so what we want is we want to compute an approximation to this
compute an approximation to this posterior all right that's our objective
后路好吧，这是我们的目标，我想你可以转弯，这很容易
posterior all right that's our objective I mean you can this turn is an easy
I mean you can this turn is an easy problem you can directly work with it so
问题，您可以直接使用它，所以您真的不需要近似值
problem you can directly work with it so you don't really need an approximation
you don't really need an approximation this chain is a going distribution but
这个链条是一个持续的分布，但是我们说很好，您知道我们想
this chain is a going distribution but we say well you know we want to
we say well you know we want to factorize QX in a nice form that is
以一种很好的形式分解QX，可以很好地分解我，所以对于每个i
factorize QX in a nice form that is factorizable i alright so for each i
factorizable i alright so for each i we're going to have the corresponding Q
我们将有相应的XI Q I，因为XI是正负2
we're going to have the corresponding Q I of X I and because X I is plus minus 2
I of X I and because X I is plus minus 2 R is discrete the only thing we need to
R是离散的，我们唯一需要用分布描述它的是
R is discrete the only thing we need to describe it with distributions is the
describe it with distributions is the mean value okay the fundamental equation
平均值好吧，我们针对每个因素得出的基本方程式
mean value okay the fundamental equation that we derived for each of this factor
that we derived for each of this factor so if you have to remind me
因此，如果您必须提醒我，那么我们进行了推导或椭圆形推导
so if you have to remind me so we did the derivation or elliptically
so we did the derivation or elliptically and we sell it factor qi or the longer
并且我们将其出售为qi或更长的拟合度，而不是干燥等于
and we sell it factor qi or the longer fits not the dry is equal to what the
fits not the dry is equal to what the expectation of
对...的期望
警察的反应是，这根本是解雇一些问题的最快速度，是极限
fits not the dry is equal to what the expectation of
police response was this fundamental to fire some problems is faster Qi is limit
警察的反应是，这根本是解雇一些问题的最快速度，是极限
fire some problems is faster Qi is limit Y is equal to
Y等于
我的意思是我可以走出去，直到你们告诉他们，他们不会休息一个小时
fire some problems is faster Qi is limit Y is equal to
I mean I can go outside they don't take a break for one hour until you guys tell
我的意思是我可以走出去，直到你们告诉他们，他们不会休息一个小时
a break for one hour until you guys tell me what the formula is whatever works
我的公式是什么管用
解决方案Qi我是一个拥有Qi索引的厨师，但它从
a break for one hour until you guys tell me what the formula is whatever works
solution Qi I'm a chef with an index there Qi but it told this from the
解决方案Qi我是一个拥有Qi索引的厨师，但它从
there Qi but it told this from the arguments the log of G is equal to the
G的对数等于对什么的期望
arguments the log of G is equal to the expectation of what
您知道，随着年龄的增长，您听到的声音会越来越少，但是这是设计使您想要删除的
you know as you get older you hear less but is by design you want to remove on
but is by design you want to remove on the knowledge all right so the rumble Qi
知识就好，所以隆隆的气就等于期望
the knowledge all right so the rumble Qi equal to the expectation
为什么你看着我我的意思是好还是不好
why you look at me I mean either it's better or not
我们对什么分配的大部分期望都寄予厚望
most of what distribution we have the expectation of the love of what
expectation of the love of what distribution before one with the other
一般而言，我们先观察到X和
distribution before one with the other in general right we had observable X and
in general right we had observable X and we had less enviable Z so what
我们的Z不那么令人羡慕，所以右边的分布是什么
we had less enviable Z so what distribution the right-hand side what
distribution the right-hand side what the question was referring to the joint
问题是指联合是一种可能性权利，即
the question was referring to the joint was a likelihood right that was the
was a likelihood right that was the starting point so the joint of like
起点，所以像把它留在这里的关节尤其可能错过了
starting point so the joint of like leave it here especially could've missed
leave it here especially could've missed all right so we started the of
好吧，所以我们开始这个因素的bit子真的是什么都没有
all right so we started the of this factor really is nothing at the
this factor really is nothing at the language of these factors is the
这些因素的语言是期望值还是请登录
language of these factors is the expectation or please doing log
expectation or please doing log likelihood which is basically minus this
基本上是减去这种能量的可能性，这就是我们
likelihood which is basically minus this energy you take the logs this is we're
energy you take the logs this is we're talking about the UH normalized thing
谈论UH归一化的东西很清楚，所以减去了能量影响
talking about the UH normalized thing clear so it's minus the energy effects
clear so it's minus the energy effects so so the number of the joint of
因此，似然的关节数显然更容易，因为这
so so the number of the joint of likelihood is obviously easier as this
likelihood is obviously easier as this right so with the - time it will be
对，所以-时间将是外部时间乘以所有时间的总和
right so with the - time it will be external times the summation of all the
external times the summation of all the neighbors of I plus ally of X I and I is
我和XI的同盟的邻居，我有很多问题，我认为这是
neighbors of I plus ally of X I and I is many many problems and I think this
many many problems and I think this reflects I to be a problem because I'm
反映出我是一个问题，因为我要说的是气的功能
reflects I to be a problem because I'm gonna said the Qi which is a function of
gonna said the Qi which is a function of X I write equal to what the expectation
十一写等于这个期望，我只想确定
X I write equal to what the expectation of this and I want to identify only the
of this and I want to identify only the terms the depend on X I write the main
依赖XI的术语会写出他们不会做的主要事情
terms the depend on X I write the main things that they wouldn't make any
things that they wouldn't make any difference in the context of excise all
消费税方面的差异还好，现在我们必须定义
difference in the context of excise all right and now we have to take to define
right and now we have to take to define the longer fly when you have to take the
当您必须对工作抱有期望时，苍蝇越长
the longer fly when you have to take the expectation of this with respect to work
我们方程式驱动熔岩坑变化的变分方法
we equation a variational methods driving the lava pits variation
driving the lava pits variation distribution dry is the expectation of
干燥分布是对这种可能性的联合期望
distribution dry is the expectation of this joint of likelihood with respect to
this joint of likelihood with respect to what horrible mean field approximation
什么可怕的平均场近似
妈妈对不起，所以当对所有人的这种痛苦期待时
this joint of likelihood with respect to what horrible mean field approximation
reversed mother sorry so when the pain expectation of this with respect to all
妈妈对不起，所以当对所有人的这种痛苦期待时
expectation of this with respect to all other body most
其他的身体，你最不想去扎达克领带
other body most you're not going to datsuk tie right
you're not going to datsuk tie right because it's a lot of re most part istic
因为在大多数情况下，您一直是他们的替代者
because it's a lot of re most part istic days you have been a substitute them
days you have been a substitute them with what my definition with there are
我的定义有很多值，因为它们的表达式
with what my definition with there are many values because their expressions
many values because their expressions are what is the mean values of XJ is
XJ的平均值在J附近是什么，所以我们说
are what is the mean values of XJ is near J alright so we said that the
near J alright so we said that the longer Qi was equal to that sir Qi is
齐等于先生齐是下一个高倍的指数
longer Qi was equal to that sir Qi is the exponential of next high times
the exponential of next high times destination over the neighbors of I plus
我的邻居的目的地加上当地的证据将取决于您
destination over the neighbors of I plus the local evidence will depend on your
the local evidence will depend on your exile alright because X I can only take
放逐是可以的，因为XI只能取值加一减一
exile alright because X I can only take values plus one and minus one there so
values plus one and minus one there so I'm introducing two different
我在这里介绍两个不同的定义。
I'm introducing two different definitions here Li plus is the value
definitions here Li plus is the value for life when X is equal to one Li minus
X等于一Li时的生命减去呼气等于
for life when X is equal to one Li minus the value of a life when exhale equal to
the value of a life when exhale equal to minus one and the reason I do this is
减一，我这样做的原因是因为X是离散的
minus one and the reason I do this is because since X is the discrete
because since X is the discrete distribution I am going to calculate the
分布我要计算X等于时的变分近似Qi
distribution I am going to calculate the variational approximation Qi at X equal
variational approximation Qi at X equal to one so with this formula William this
一个这样的公式威廉这个呃归一化的分配权是
to one so with this formula William this uh normalized distribution right that's
uh normalized distribution right that's why you have this symbol here do you
为什么在这里有此符号，您是否相信-例如-1是
why you have this symbol here do you believe that - I for example - 1 is
believe that - I for example - 1 is equal to really let's call this whole
等于真的让我们在这里称这整个总和为好，所以这
equal to really let's call this whole summation here mi alright so this
summation here mi alright so this conservation work all is mi so we agreed
保护工作都是mi，所以我们同意qi 4 x等于1就是1
conservation work all is mi so we agreed that qi 4 x equals 1 is this would be 1
that qi 4 x equals 1 is this would be 1 so you need to the mi + x I equal 1 plus
因此您需要将mi + x I等于1加li加除以该归一化
so you need to the mi + x I equal 1 plus li plus divided by this normalization
li plus divided by this normalization factor
因素
好吧，如果我写这个，我可以这样做
li plus divided by this normalization factor
right okay if I write this I can do it like this
好吧，如果我写这个，我可以这样做
if I write this I can do it like this and immediately you see that this
然后您立即发现这种流量周期将被采用
and immediately you see that this traffic cycles one comes to be employed
traffic cycles one comes to be employed okay so that's a very nice result
好吧，这是一个非常不错的结果，好吧，同样，七月的身体
okay so that's a very nice result okay and and similarly the body of july
okay and and similarly the body of july 4 ik cycle -1 comes to be this 2.4
4 ik周期-1成为这个2.4参数--AI的AI很好
4 ik cycle -1 comes to be this 2.4 argument - - AI for AI is this nice
argument - - AI for AI is this nice there appear a my that we said this
似乎有一个我说过的蒸馏法，因为这些是
there appear a my that we said this distillation known because these are the
distillation known because these are the means of the neighbors plus 0.5 li plus
邻居的平均值加上0.5 li加-2 ly-也知道所以
means of the neighbors plus 0.5 li plus -2 ly - also know so the main view of
-2 ly - also know so the main view of the discrete the various on distribution
当X-1时XI的离散分布基本上是纯高的。
the discrete the various on distribution of X I is basically pure high when X - 1
of X I is basically pure high when X - 1 times the volume which 1 plus this time
乘以1加上这次的值减去1得出的音量，如果这样的话
times the volume which 1 plus this time from the values minus 1 and if you such
from the values minus 1 and if you such gives you all of these things you get to
给您所有这些东西，您就可以得到平均值，是dong是双曲线
gives you all of these things you get to the mean values is dong is the hyperbola
the mean values is dong is the hyperbola target basically of AI ok also very nice
基本上以AI为目标，效果也很好，因此更新公式
target basically of AI ok also very nice result and so the update formulas
result and so the update formulas basically if I can write verse
基本上，如果我能明确地写诗是，
basically if I can write verse explicitly is that the mean value of
explicitly is that the mean value of every variable I is the hyperbolic
每个变量我都是您在这些变量中看到的双曲正切值
every variable I is the hyperbolic tangent of what you see inside these
tangent of what you see inside these parentheses obviously to update the UI
括号显然要更新UI，您需要知道
parentheses obviously to update the UI you need to know the mean of the
you need to know the mean of the neighborhood so this equation can only
邻域，因此只能求解此等式
neighborhood so this equation can only be solved
be solved instead constant right so you have to
而是恒定的权利，因此您必须进行迭代，显然您可以执行此操作
instead constant right so you have to iterate and obviously you can do this
iterate and obviously you can do this with a lots of color nice tricks you can
带有很多颜色的漂亮技巧，您可以遍历每个像素并重复
with a lots of color nice tricks you can go through each of the pixels and repeat
go through each of the pixels and repeat this until basically converges or you
直到基本收敛为止，或者即使在同步模型中也可以做到这一点
this until basically converges or you can do it even in a synchronous model ok
can do it even in a synchronous model ok the so the interrelations look like this
因此，相互关系看起来像这样，所以如果您在此处放置一个索引棒
the so the interrelations look like this so if you put an index stick here for
so if you put an index stick here for the iterations you use the previous
您使用先前的迭代，无论您拥有的值是什么，更新mi
the iterations you use the previous whatever values you have the update mi
whatever values you have the update mi and you keep going and then
然后继续走下去，如果您
and you keep going and then more often you will see this in if you
more often you will see this in if you download programs that do this you
下载执行此操作的程序，您实际上会将此方程式与一些
download programs that do this you actually apply this equation with some
actually apply this equation with some relaxation so rather than using this
放松，而不是使用新的值，而是使用凸音
relaxation so rather than using this value for new I you use a convex sound
value for new I you use a convex sound basically of the previous values plus
基本上是先前值加上预测的值
basically of the previous values plus the value that is predicted to
the value that is predicted to variational networks okay so this is
变体网络还可以，因此这是一种更稳定的方法，可以避免
variational networks okay so this is sort of way more stable and avoids a
sort of way more stable and avoids a number of effects but usually are common
效果数量，但是当我尝试给您一个效果时，通常在组合模型中很常见
number of effects but usually are common in uniting models when I try give you an
in uniting models when I try give you an example and the example is basically you
这个例子，这个例子基本上是可以运行的，它在数学水晶盒中
example and the example is basically you can run it it's in math crystal box do I
can run it it's in math crystal box do I have to do is once you install it you
要做的是，一旦安装它，您就会发现马自达噪音很美
have to do is once you install it you just with a nice thing a Mazda noise
just with a nice thing a Mazda noise demo and it will get your results and
演示，它将获得您的结果，并且您仅可以保存漂亮的程序十个
demo and it will get your results and you can save the nice program only ten
you can save the nice program only ten lines that can solve this little problem
行可以解决这个小问题，好吧，这是您从嘈杂的声音开始
lines that can solve this little problem okay so this is you start with a noisy
okay so this is you start with a noisy image you know obviously you have used
您知道的图像您显然已经使用过，例如，需要使用一些参数
image you know obviously you have used need to use some parameters for example
need to use some parameters for example this part a long time in this relaxation
这是您在放松方法中花了很长时间才知道的部分，但是您可以
this part a long time in this relaxation method that's how you know but you can
method that's how you know but you can see mmediately the methodologies are
立即看到这些方法能够识别出实际的图像
see mmediately the methodologies are able to recognize what the actual image
able to recognize what the actual image is and so this is the mean of the
是，所以这是违规后验的后验的均值
is and so this is the mean of the posterior of the violation posterior
posterior of the violation posterior after a number of 15 strips purity all
经过15条剥离后，图像中的所有像素均被纯度
after a number of 15 strips purity all the pixels in the image
好的
all right
所以我要成为的是您知道这里有太多的材料要覆盖，
so I'm going to be you know there is way too much material to be covered here and
too much material to be covered here and this is an important topic I need to be
这是一个重要的话题，我需要确保我们或多或少地讨论了
this is an important topic I need to be sure that we discussed more or less the
sure that we discussed more or less the most important things
最重要的事情，所以让我跳上幻灯片
most important things so let me I'm going to jump on the slide
so let me I'm going to jump on the slide and go to slides at the age of any
并在任何年龄都去看幻灯片，提醒我一次回到幻灯片31
and go to slides at the age of any remind me to come back to slide 31 once
remind me to come back to slide 31 once we're done so let me do another very
我们已经完成了，所以让我再举一个非常简单的例子，除非我们已经有了
we're done so let me do another very simple example unless we already have
simple example unless we already have done it if you would do this example
如果您要以高斯为例进行此示例，请完成此操作，如果它是单位
done it if you would do this example with the Gaussian okay if it's the unit
with the Gaussian okay if it's the unit to to get out but we did it just let me
要出去，但我们做到了，只是让我知道好吧，因为我做得太多了
to to get out but we did it just let me know okay because I'm doing too much
know okay because I'm doing too much jumping here all right so let's suppose
跳到这里好吧，让我们假设我们来自高斯，但这是一个
jumping here all right so let's suppose we from a Gaussian but here's a
we from a Gaussian but here's a precision tau and a mean mu but we don't
精度tau和平均亩，但我们不知道还可以，典型的视觉推断
precision tau and a mean mu but we don't know okay and typical vision inference
know okay and typical vision inference problem is to calculate the posterior of
问题是要计算MU和tau的后验
problem is to calculate the posterior of MU and tau and again for what we have
MU and tau and again for what we have taken Bayesian inference cost is like
采取贝叶斯推断成本就像成本一样有一个解析
taken Bayesian inference cost is like the cost there is an analytical
the cost there is an analytical calculation basically gives you the
计算基本上给您后验者，但我想做的是
calculation basically gives you the posteriors exactly but what I want to do
posteriors exactly but what I want to do is I want sort of to use the variational
我想使用变分方法，以便我们可以了解它们的工作原理和
is I want sort of to use the variational method so we can see how they work and
method so we can see how they work and how good they do so I'm going to take
他们做得如何，所以我要带巴黎公社tau成为什么
how good they do so I'm going to take the Paris Commune tau to be what's
the Paris Commune tau to be what's called a normal gamma distribution so
称为正态伽马分布，因此给定tau，MU的分布为
called a normal gamma distribution so given tau the distribution of MU is a
given tau the distribution of MU is a Gaussian and then for the precision of
高斯，然后为了精度从显示在这
Gaussian and then for the precision of comes from showing the in this
comes from showing the in this distribution you put a gamma
分布，您将伽玛分布作为供应商还可以，所以这
distribution you put a gamma distribution as a supplier okay so this
distribution as a supplier okay so this is the priors and for this priors and
是先验的，对于这个先验，这很可能具有合理的道德
is the priors and for this priors and it's likely with the reasonable ethical
it's likely with the reasonable ethical solution for the posterior we pretend we
我们假装的后验解决方案我们不知道我们的解决方案在哪里
solution for the posterior we pretend we don't know where our solution is we
don't know where our solution is we don't really care right now and what we
现在真的不在乎，我们要做的是
don't really care right now and what we want to do is we want to
want to do is we want to you know we want to calculate the
您知道我们想计算后验变化并使用均值
you know we want to calculate the variation posterior and using the mean
variation posterior and using the mean field approximation we're going to
场近似，我们将施肥，关节将是
field approximation we're going to fertilize it the joint is going to be
fertilize it the joint is going to be written as somebody s and distribution
写为某人和发行人Emil和某人在分发
written as somebody s and distribution Emil and somebody s in distribution of
Emil and somebody s in distribution of how but we immediately see that this is
但是，我们立即看到这将是一个近似值
how but we immediately see that this is going to be an approximation right
going to be an approximation right because for those who have looked at
因为对于那些在没有确切解决方案之前就已经看过这个问题的人
because for those who have looked at this problem before the exact solution
this problem before the exact solution you expect basically if the pious look
您基本上希望虔诚的表情看起来像指数
you expect basically if the pious look like that this is to the exponential
like that this is to the exponential family the posterior is going to be on
家庭后验将在指数上它将是
family the posterior is going to be on the exponents it's going to be a
the exponents it's going to be a Gaussian in the ocean gamma for example
例如，这里的tau是海洋伽马中的高斯，因此您期望
Gaussian in the ocean gamma for example for here tau so you expect the
for here tau so you expect the prosthetics for me and how to have this
我的义肢，以及如何以mu 0 lambda 0和
prosthetics for me and how to have this for well in terms of mu 0 lambda 0 and
for well in terms of mu 0 lambda 0 and alpha 0 MV 0 you have some mu and
alpha 0 MV 0您有一些亩和亚特兰大，还有n的alpha N和B n
alpha 0 MV 0 you have some mu and Atlanta and an alpha N and B n for n
Atlanta and an alpha N and B n for n data points obviously business and state
数据显然以这种形式指向业务和状态，因为
data points obviously business and state in that form because the distribution of
in that form because the distribution of you does not involve tau so
您不涉及tau这样的近似值，所以您知道我们需要
you does not involve tau so approximation so it you know we need to
approximation so it you know we need to see you know if things make sense right
看到你知道事情是否合理显然你不会这么做
see you know if things make sense right obviously you are not going to do this
obviously you are not going to do this in reality okay but in this class
在现实中还可以，但是在这一堂课中没有最优公式
in reality okay but in this class there's no reality formula the optimal
there's no reality formula the optimal KJ is the expectation is where all the
KJ是关节对数的所有其他变量的期望值
KJ is the expectation is where all the other variables of the log of the joint
other variables of the log of the joint of likelihood so I am going to start
很有可能，所以我将在此计算中开始使用它
of likelihood so I am going to start playing with this in this calculation
playing with this in this calculation you need to get really understand it all
您需要完全了解它，因为您知道是否知道
you need to get really understand it all right because you know if you know the
right because you know if you know the study you will never see you will not
研究你永远不会看到你不会对这些推导有任何意义
study you will never see you will not make any sense of these derivations
make any sense of these derivations little children many infinite settings
小孩子很多无限的设置好吧，所以你必须通过这些工作
little children many infinite settings okay so you have to work through these
okay so you have to work through these little problems okay so let's change we
小问题好了，让我们进行更改，我们要更新版本
little problems okay so let's change we want let's update the variation
want let's update the variation distribution for me oh okay so we're
分配给我哦，好吧，我们要对
distribution for me oh okay so we're gonna take expectation with respect to
gonna take expectation with respect to all the
所有的瓦拉姆松散只有一个或
all the varam loose there's only one or the
varam loose there's only one or the bottom which is tau so here the joint
底部是tau，所以在这里看起来像我们可以的联合
bottom which is tau so here the joint look like we could it would be the
look like we could it would be the likelihood of the data all right which
数据正确的可能性是高斯，这些记忆消失了
likelihood of the data all right which is Gaussian and these remember disappear
is Gaussian and these remember disappear and there's a problem you given tau and
而且您给了tau并在tau上先给了一个问题，但由于我们很感兴趣
and there's a problem you given tau and prior on tau but since we are interested
prior on tau but since we are interested in the distribution of Mew
在Mew的发行中，任何不依赖您的东西我们
in the distribution of Mew anything that does not depend on you we
anything that does not depend on you we don't play with okay so the prior and
不要玩，所以先验和tau是常数，所以如果您扩展
don't play with okay so the prior and tau is with a constant so if you expand
tau is with a constant so if you expand this if you're going to get something
如果你要得到这样的权利
this if you're going to get something like this right
like this right this ranges from you that's the only
这是您的事，这是我们扩展的唯一机会，让您来
this ranges from you that's the only time we get if we expand let you come
time we get if we expand let you come can somebody tell it's important if this
有人可以说这件事是否有下降测验这个学期目标很重要
can somebody tell it's important if this thing have drop quiz this term target
所以这来自那里可能的可能性
so this came from the the likelihood there all right
there all right okay and the query is to this time
好的，查询到现在为止是从您开始计算的。
okay and the query is to this time counting from you given top okay which
counting from you given top okay which is Gaussian okay so and you remember the
是高斯的，所以，您还记得那是lambda 0倍的精度
is Gaussian okay so and you remember the precision of that it was lambda 0 times
precision of that it was lambda 0 times tau so obviously you're gonna get 1 2 0
tau很明显，你会得到1 2 0倍的tau，但是Tau变成了期望
tau so obviously you're gonna get 1 2 0 times tau but the Tau became expectation
times tau but the Tau became expectation of tau Y because every queries any time
的原因，因为每一次询问我们都需要期望就可以了
of tau Y because every queries any time we need to take expectations okay
we need to take expectations okay and again the rest terms that depend
其余仅依赖于不依赖于视图的术语
and again the rest terms that depend only on on the don't depend on view we
only on on the don't depend on view we don't include them okay so you look at
不要把它们包括在内，所以无论您使用哪种发行版，您都可以看到它
don't include them okay so you look at this nice whatever distribution do you
this nice whatever distribution do you think you will get here if you play for
我想如果你以此计算玩了五分钟你会到达这里
think you will get here if you play for five minutes with this calculation I
five minutes with this calculation I mean we need a distribution of you know
意味着我们需要您知道的分布，并且我向您发送一个新的正方形和一个正方形
mean we need a distribution of you know and I stream u square a new square and a
and I stream u square a new square and a linear term in una Linea Turing new plus
una中的线性项Linea Turing新加常数，因此显然会闭合平方
linear term in una Linea Turing new plus constant so obviously closing the square
constant so obviously closing the square we're gonna get a Gaussian distribution
我们将获得这种花园传统的高斯分布
we're gonna get a Gaussian distribution of this garden tradition you can so with
of this garden tradition you can so with zero time has this mean and has this
零时间具有该均值，并且具有这种精度，所以X是样本
zero time has this mean and has this precision okay and so X is the sample
precision okay and so X is the sample mean basically this is for the data come
基本上意味着这是因为数据来自于先前的lambda n
mean basically this is for the data come from this comes from the prior lambda n
from this comes from the prior lambda n involves the precision of tau in
涉及到tau的精度立即提醒您，因为我们
involves the precision of tau in immediately that reminds you because we
immediately that reminds you because we don't know that the posterior but
不知道后路，但是我们需要做些什么
don't know that the posterior but somehow we're gonna need to do
somehow we're gonna need to do iterations so basically to compute this
迭代，因此基本上要计算此分布，您需要知道
iterations so basically to compute this distribution you need to know what the
distribution you need to know what the mean of tau it's okay so we need to go
牛头意味着没有问题，所以我们需要计算一下
mean of tau it's okay so we need to go and compute off
所以同样离开了我们，我们对所有人都寄予了厚望
so similarly left the power again we have big expectation with respect to all
have big expectation with respect to all the other variables which dearest meal
其他变量，这些变量最珍惜事前的可能性
the other variables which dearest meal of the likelihood the prior of being
of the likelihood the prior of being given tau and the prior of power has to
给定tau且必须包含功率的先验，因为我们感兴趣
given tau and the prior of power has to be included because we're interested of
be included because we're interested of the distribution of tau so this term
tau的分布，所以这个术语来自数据的可能性，所以
the distribution of tau so this term comes from the data likelihood so
comes from the data likelihood so obviously didn't be an ex-professional
显然不是一个专业人士，期待您来自此，所以
obviously didn't be an ex-professional expecting you this comes from this so
expecting you this comes from this so it's going to be an expectation respect
这将是对用餐的期望，这东西是从哪里来的
it's going to be an expectation respect to meal where is this thing coming from
to meal where is this thing coming from one of those two terms the first two
这两个术语中的一个，前两个术语来自幂一的先验
one of those two terms the first two terms coming from the prior of power I
terms coming from the prior of power I PI of tau which is a gamma distribution
tau的PI是伽马分布，那两个项在哪里
PI of tau which is a gamma distribution all right and where are those two terms
all right and where are those two terms coming from
来自（哪里
记住，在使用此发行版之前，我们只保留条款
all right and where are those two terms coming from
remember when before we play with this distribution okay we only kept the terms
记住，在使用此发行版之前，我们只保留条款
distribution okay we only kept the terms but involve me do you have to keep all
但要让我参与进来，您是否必须保留涉及陶的所有条款，所以您可以
but involve me do you have to keep all the terms that involve Tao so can you
the terms that involve Tao so can you tell me where let's say there is it
告诉我在哪里，那里是什么，然后从那里来
tell me where let's say there is it there what is this then coming from
所以让我回去提醒你所有的一切，以便当一个高贵的人去做时
so let me go back for you to remind you all everything so when a nobler to do
all everything so when a nobler to do with power comes from from the
力量来自于可能性，你会注意到
with power comes from from the likelihood and you notice there is
likelihood and you notice there is another person coming from there
另一个人从那里来，所以可以吗，所以我们有
another person coming from there all right so for is it okay so we have
all right so for is it okay so we have this term Plus this term so effectively
这个学期加上这个学期，如此有效，如果你看的话，你需要做什么
this term Plus this term so effectively what you need to do if you look at it
what you need to do if you look at it carefully it is the log of the gamma
仔细地，它是伽马分布的对数，所以在正常情况下
carefully it is the log of the gamma distribution alright so in the normal
distribution alright so in the normal distribution when you take logs you get
分配原木时，会得到大量的tau和粉末，因此您
distribution when you take logs you get a lot of tau and a powder so that you
a lot of tau and a powder so that you put all the locks of tau together and
把tau的所有锁和所有权力术语放在一起
put all the locks of tau together and all the power terms together alright
all the power terms together alright what you will get is you will get a
您会得到的是，您将获得这种类型的伽玛分布
what you will get is you will get a gamma distribution for this type of
gamma distribution for this type of alpha 0 you have our fire and instead of
alpha 0，您拥有我们的火力，而不是bazzill，您拥有beta N，再次在这里
alpha 0 you have our fire and instead of bazzill you have beta N and again here
bazzill you have beta N and again here you need to have expectation with
您需要对MU有所期望，而无需全力以赴
you need to have expectation with respect to MU and don't need to do all
respect to MU and don't need to do all of this so basically this distribution
因此，基本上所有qfm的分布汇总都是高斯分布
of this so basically this distribution summary of everything qfm is a Gaussian
summary of everything qfm is a Gaussian feel power is a gamma distribution the
感觉力量是伽玛分布，参数以您看到的方式定义
feel power is a gamma distribution the parameters are defined the way you see
parameters are defined the way you see them here you can see to define the mean
他们在这里您可以看到定义您需要知道的Q Prem的均值
them here you can see to define the mean the variance of Q Prem you need to know
the variance of Q Prem you need to know the mean of tau in the ministry remember
内务部tau的均值记住正态分布，该均值
the mean of tau in the ministry remember for a normal distribution which the mean
for a normal distribution which the mean if you have gamma distribution of the
如果您的止损点有伽玛分布，则beta代表任何人
if you have gamma distribution of the stop and beta would the mean anybody
stop and beta would the mean anybody remembers alpha divided by beta all
记得可以用alpha除以beta，所以您可以立即看到
remembers alpha divided by beta all right so you can see immediately that
right so you can see immediately that the mean of tau depends on Alpha and
tau的平均值取决于Alpha和Beta n，后者又取决于
the mean of tau depends on Alpha and Beta n which again depends on moments of
Beta n which again depends on moments of alright so we need to know the
好吧，所以我们需要知道您的分布，所以您需要
alright so we need to know the distribution of you so what you need to
distribution of you so what you need to do is you need to iterate ok it's like
要做的是，您需要进行迭代，好吧，就像您从某人的背心开始，然后
do is you need to iterate ok it's like you start with somebody's vest then you
you start with somebody's vest then you compute gamma then you find the moments
计算伽玛值，然后您便会发现当下所知道的瞬间
compute gamma then you find the moments you know whatever that the expectation
you know whatever that the expectation of star
的星星，你回到计算器
of star you go back you to calculators keep
you go back you to calculators keep going i fiddle basically convert sense
我正在摆弄小提琴，基本上可以转换感官，这是一个小例子
going i fiddle basically convert sense and and here is sort of a little example
and and here is sort of a little example I don't know yes so there is a Python
我不知道是的，所以诺言再写了一个Python代码
I don't know yes so there is a Python code written by the promise didn't again
code written by the promise didn't again but you can download and I think I you
但您可以下载，我想我知道此链接已得到纠正，但是其中一些
but you can download and I think I you know this link is corrected but some of
know this link is corrected but some of the links I need to double check that
我需要仔细检查的链接是否合理，所以这是
the links I need to double check that they're making sense so okay so this is
they're making sense so okay so this is one of the estimation of this cube meal
如果您更新功率，则通过提示更新来估算此立方餐的其中之一
one of the estimation of this cube meal with cue update if you update your power
with cue update if you update your power and then when it converges in the
然后当它在过程中收敛时，就是实际的分布
and then when it converges in the process is the actual distribution that
process is the actual distribution that history with this I am assuming red or
与此相关的历史我假设是红色或绿色护理好的，所以这又一次
history with this I am assuming red or green care okay alright so this again
green care okay alright so this again it's a female example by we know the
这是一个女性的例子，因为我们知道分析方法，但是如果您认为
it's a female example by we know the analytical solution but if you think
analytical solution but if you think about it you know the test of greenness
关于它，您知道绿色计算的测试是微不足道的，但是您知道
about it you know the test of greenness calculation is trivial and but you know
calculation is trivial and but you know if the reason is the solution
如果原因是解决方案，那么您很抱歉不能使用
if the reason is the solution unfortunately you cannot go by but using
unfortunately you cannot go by but using only the analytical solution and if
仅分析溶液，如果有分析溶液，则您
only the analytical solution and if there is an analytical solution you
there is an analytical solution you pretend you don't really know that's
假装你真的不知道这对你很不好，就像你真正需要的那样
pretend you don't really know that's very bad for you like actually you need
very bad for you like actually you need to know okay but this problem with is
知道可以，但是这个问题有点类似于退出，退出，退出，操作好
to know okay but this problem with is sort of exit exit exit ops okay
正确的
right
抱歉，我想担任一个职位，我将在其他提示中重复
in sorry I want to make a position that I'm gonna repeat for other prompts as
I'm gonna repeat for other prompts as well right when you remember we we when
好吧，当您还记得我们的时候，我们就开始了变分方法吧
well right when you remember we we when we started the variational methods right
we started the variational methods right we solve that we define what's going to
我们解决了，我们定义了将要了解的所有知识，这就是数量
we solve that we define what's going to know about all right and this was amount
know about all right and this was amount to what the entity to the right legal
对实体具有适当的法律效力还可以吗？您需要做的一件事情
to what the entity to the right legal effects okay one of the things you need
effects okay one of the things you need to do when you're I this Court's right
当你是我的时候，这个法院的权利是性地完成下限
to do when you're I this Court's right is to sexually complete the lower bound
is to sexually complete the lower bound because the objective invariants are
因为客观不变式是您要做很多事情的推论
because the objective invariants are inferences to do what you want to much
inferences to do what you want to much tomorrow is the log-likelihood right and
明天是对数可能性，因为您不需要我的太多
tomorrow is the log-likelihood right and because you don't need too much to my
because you don't need too much to my eyes well below bow so you know you
弓下方的眼睛很好，所以您知道您别无选择，只能计算一个
eyes well below bow so you know you really have no choice but to compute a
really have no choice but to compute a lot of also in other ways if you do all
很多其他方式，如果您正确处理了所有情况，则从一个开始
lot of also in other ways if you do all of the situation's right you go from one
of the situation's right you go from one iteration to another this question is
迭代到另一个这个问题是你能告诉我实际上没有多少
iteration to another this question is can you show me for no amount actually
can you show me for no amount actually increases during iterations because if
在迭代过程中会增加，因为如果这样做，那么无论您有什么兴趣
increases during iterations because if it does then whatever interests is you
it does then whatever interests is you do it's magic is not science you need to
这样做是不是科学的魔术，您需要持续显示下半身
do it's magic is not science you need to show that the lower body continuously
show that the lower body continuously increases okay so we need to compute the
可以增加，所以我们现在需要计算较低的值，这就是标准
increases okay so we need to compute the lower now that's the standard
lower now that's the standard calculation you have to do in this
您必须在这种近似变分方法中进行计算，所以让我们
calculation you have to do in this approximate variational method so let's
approximate variational method so let's try to do the lower bound for the simple
尝试为高斯的简单情况做一个下界，所以我要
try to do the lower bound for the simple case of the Gaussian so I'm going to
case of the Gaussian so I'm going to remind you the calculation it's also bad
提醒您计算也很糟糕，但是它的标准功能是可以做到两次或
remind you the calculation it's also bad but its standard it will do it two or
but its standard it will do it two or three or four problems you will be able
三个或四个问题，您将能够在与研究相关的研究中真正做到这一点
three or four problems you will be able to actually do this in research related
to actually do this in research related problems in machine learning
机器学习中的问题还可以，所以我提醒您
problems in machine learning okay so the I remind you it's the
okay so the I remind you it's the expectation with respect to the
关于变化分布的期望以保证
expectation with respect to the variational distribution to guarantee
variational distribution to guarantee which we factorize it and of the log of
我们将其分解为联合倡议罩的对数，然后我将其写成
which we factorize it and of the log of the joint initiative hood and I wrote it
the joint initiative hood and I wrote it here explicitly this is my date of the
在这里，这显然是我的MU和功效日期除以方差
here explicitly this is my date of the MU and power divided by the variance
MU and power divided by the variance the tradition and then I mean how is the
传统，然后我的意思是伟大的力量如何
the tradition and then I mean how is the great power
great power alright this is the definition we use
好吧，这就是我们使用的定义，它是一个小炸弹，所以要超出这个范围
alright this is the definition we use that's a little bomb so to exceed this
that's a little bomb so to exceed this alright so I'm going to make this Q and
好吧，所以我要问这个Q并用期望值代替
alright so I'm going to make this Q and substituted with expectation of the
substituted with expectation of the arguments right this is the expectation
正确的论点，这是伊斯兰对这种变化的期望
arguments right this is the expectation of Islam with respect to this variation
of Islam with respect to this variation distribution Q so that's what II refers
分布Q，所以我在这里指的是II，因此我对
distribution Q so that's what II refers here so I have the expectation of the
here so I have the expectation of the log of the numerator which I can write
分子的日志，我可以将其写入我们已经给出的喜欢的日志
log of the numerator which I can write it the log of the likes we've given the
it the log of the likes we've given the parameters and then I have the prior log
参数，然后我具有先前给定塔的水平的先验日志
parameters and then I have the prior log of the prior given tower level of the
of the prior given tower level of the prior power you see that this counts by
您可以通过将其写为时间的生命来了解这一点
prior power you see that this counts by writing this as the life of the time
writing this as the life of the time supplier
供应商没事，然后再结账
supplier all right nothing else and then Bill
all right nothing else and then Bill denominator because this is factorize I
分母，因为这是分解因素我有期望，所有这些
denominator because this is factorize I have expectations and all these
have expectations and all these expectations of the law of pure fair and
对纯粹公平法则的期望和很多屋顶确实可以，所以如果
expectations of the law of pure fair and a lot of rooftop really all right so if
a lot of rooftop really all right so if you need to do you need to go and and
您需要做的是，去计算所有步骤，这样就可以
you need to do you need to go and and compute all of the steps okay it makes a
compute all of the steps okay it makes a massive task and this is only a
艰巨的任务，这只是一个单变量的高斯，所以你应该
massive task and this is only a univariate gaussians so you should be
univariate gaussians so you should be able to to live with it okay so let's
能够忍受它，好吧，让我们来看一下如果您愿意的话
able to to live with it okay so let's see let's pick up the easy terms if you
see let's pick up the easy terms if you take one more fuel and what type of
女权主义者多喝一种燃料，以及自我分配的类型
take one more fuel and what type of distribution self you feminists
它变成了高斯子爵的，很明显是对的，所以当你有
it came to be a Gaussian viscount's and clear right so when you have the
clear right so when you have the expected obviously there is not here
预期显然这里没有，所以期望与
expected obviously there is not here alright so the expectation was with
alright so the expectation was with respect to me on power but this now
尊重我的权力，但这现在成为期望您的期望
respect to me on power but this now becomes expectation expecting you so
becomes expectation expecting you so leave me what you have here is nothing
离开我，你在这里拥有的就是这个高斯的熵
leave me what you have here is nothing else not the entropy of this Gaussian
else not the entropy of this Gaussian distribution so you can look in
分布，所以您可以查看Wikipedia并说熵列表
distribution so you can look in Wikipedia and say entropy list there's
Wikipedia and say entropy list there's the answer okay alright so this is the
答案很好，所以这是QP的熵就是
the answer okay alright so this is the entropy of QP would be the entropy of
entropy of QP would be the entropy of the gamma distribution you can again
当我75分钟后，您可以再次查看Wikipedia的伽马分布
the gamma distribution you can again look at Wikipedia 75 minutes when I
look at Wikipedia 75 minutes when I check these things right there is
检查这些东西对您有无处不在的信息
check these things right there is information everywhere around you in
information everywhere around you in case you don't remember this is what's
如果你不记得这就是所谓的我的伽玛分布
case you don't remember this is what's called the my gamma distribution that
called the my gamma distribution that appears in the gamma distribution sin it
出现在伽玛分布中，它也出现在分布中，所以这
appears in the gamma distribution sin it also appears in the distribution so this
also appears in the distribution so this is it so this is the by gamma
就是这样，这是伽玛分布，好吧，我不会告诉你
is it so this is the by gamma distribution okay I'm not gonna tell you
distribution okay I'm not gonna tell you what it is you can look and I trust
您可以看到什么，我相信印度那里有一个链接，他们
what it is you can look and I trust there is a link there of India and they
there is a link there of India and they were not really computers there was no
不是真正的计算机，没有维基百科，没有书籍
were not really computers there was no Wikipedia there were no books they were
Wikipedia there were no books they were not PDFs of Chinese origin or anything
不是中国血统的PDF或类似的东西，一切都很干净
not PDFs of Chinese origin or anything like that everything was nice and clean
like that everything was nice and clean some with some library and you have to
有些有一些图书馆，你必须花五个小时才能找到它
some with some library and you have to go and spend five hours to locate it in
go and spend five hours to locate it in a library here are you know two minutes
这里有图书馆，您知道两分钟就可以了，但显然您在
a library here are you know two minutes where it is alright but obviously you're
where it is alright but obviously you're given something immediately means the
立即得到某事意味着您对某事的期望
given something immediately means the expectations that you do something with
expectations that you do something with other are higher all right because this
其他较高，因为您需要此信息区域来做用户
other are higher all right because this information area you need to do user
information area you need to do user information no excuses for not
信息没有借口，因为没有固定好吧，如此复杂的条款，我们
information no excuses for not fixed all right so complicated terms we
fixed all right so complicated terms we need now the expectation of the logo PI
现在需要T的徽标PI相对于T的Q的期望，所以我继续
need now the expectation of the logo PI of T with respect to Q of T so I keep
of T with respect to Q of T so I keep the expectation outside I'm expanding
外界的期望正在扩大伽玛分布的对数，因此
the expectation outside I'm expanding the log of gamma distribution so there
the log of gamma distribution so there is nothing here bizarre from the
从规范化术语来看，这里没有什么奇怪的，好吗
is nothing here bizarre from the normalization terms okay
normalization terms okay this comes from you know remember the
这来自您，知道伽玛分布是塔12加0
this comes from you know remember the gamma distribution is tower 12 plus 0
gamma distribution is tower 12 plus 0 minus 1 tau 2 minus B you got 2 minus
减1 tau 2减B，您得到2减beta 0对或减的最大交易
minus 1 tau 2 minus B you got 2 minus beta 0 right or biggest deal to minus
beta 0 right or biggest deal to minus tau which was it yeah okay something
牛头是的，是的，好吧，一些你知道的东西，像那样的东西
tau which was it yeah okay something something you know something like that
something you know something like that okay so okay so let me see there must be
好吧好吧，让我看看这里一定有一个漏掉的词，所以我需要挖掘一下
okay so okay so let me see there must be a missing term here so I need to dig
a missing term here so I need to dig expectations this with respect to Q P
就QP而言，期望如此，并且这个术语在这个术语中是不变的
expectations this with respect to Q P okay and this term is constant this term
okay and this term is constant this term is constant
一直都很好，我们现在需要做的是您需要
is constant okay what we need to do now is you need
okay what we need to do now is you need the expectation of the longest power
关于Q tau和立方时间的最大功效的期望是
the expectation of the longest power with respect to Q tau and cube time is
with respect to Q tau and cube time is for distribution is gamma surprised
伽玛感到惊讶，因为有一个非常著名的公式
for distribution is gamma surprised there's a very famous formula becomes
there's a very famous formula becomes very often actually in machine learning
实际上，在机器学习中，它通常不是伽玛分布
very often actually in machine learning it's not as a gamma distribution we have
it's not as a gamma distribution we have expectations with respect to the gamma
关于tau的爱的伽玛分布的期望
expectations with respect to the gamma distribution of the love of tau the
distribution of the love of tau the result is the by gamma distribution
结果是按伽玛分布计算的，因此如果Nama
result is the by gamma distribution calculated on so if the Nama
calculated on so if the Nama distribution starts a and B so this
分布以a和B开头，因此三角形的减数为theta的三角形轨迹
distribution starts a and B so this triangle trace of a minus log of theta
triangle trace of a minus log of theta okay and some course you need to compute
好的，您当然需要计算伽玛分布的均值
okay and some course you need to compute the mean of a gamma distribution which
the mean of a gamma distribution which is a over beta so basically you're done
是一个超过Beta的测试版，因此基本上您已经用完了这个词
is a over beta so basically you're done with this term as well this is premium
with this term as well this is premium because this Gaussian
因为这个高斯这就是高斯所以
because this Gaussian this is Gaussian so
this is Gaussian so I am just giving you the results that
我只是给你结果，你可以暴露
I am just giving you the results that you expose okay
you expose okay and you yours the sufficient statistics
而且您每天的统计数据足以简化您的操作
and you yours the sufficient statistics of the day to simplify you get this nice
of the day to simplify you get this nice results stimulus for this is a Gaussian
结果刺激是高斯的，您可以扩展，这是最终的结果
results stimulus for this is a Gaussian okay you expand and this is the final
okay you expand and this is the final formula okay
公式好吧，它看起来非常复杂，您可能
formula okay it looks very complicated and you may
it looks very complicated and you may ask me I'm like so kind to you putting
问我，我对你这么好，把所有这些东西都换成不同的颜色，不
ask me I'm like so kind to you putting all these things in different colors no
all these things in different colors no you know why I put them in colors
你知道为什么我把它们涂成彩色，因为当我推导它的时候，我一直
you know why I put them in colors because when I was deriving this I keep
because when I was deriving this I keep doing mistakes so I wanted to know that
犯了错误，所以我想知道这与什么相结合，所以我会带它去做
doing mistakes so I wanted to know that combines with what so I will bring it
combines with what so I will bring it for myself because you know this is the
对我自己，因为你知道这是我现在可以学到的唯一方法，如果
for myself because you know this is the only way I can learn all right now if
only way I can learn all right now if you want to take advance of the course -
您想继续学习该课程-如果一起学习为什么他们可以在那工作呢
you want to take advance of the course - and if together why they work there okay
and if together why they work there okay so this time something would be the same
所以这一次，当您完成时，某些颜色将是相同的颜色
so this time something would be the same color combined and when you're finished
color combined and when you're finished if you get let me see if there is a you
如果你让我看看是否有一个，你实际上做了一个非常琐碎的事情
if you get let me see if there is a you did actually an extremely trivial
did actually an extremely trivial formula okay I'm surprised myself
公式好吧，我感到很惊讶-显然有很多取消
formula okay I'm surprised myself - obviously lots of cancellations the
- obviously lots of cancellations the loan amount is - well half of ll of long
贷款金额为-长期租约的一半，还可以加上本地程序员
loan amount is - well half of ll of long tenure okay Plus local programmer
tenure okay Plus local programmer function computer the N minus a and log
功能计算机N减去a和BN的对数，我提醒您这是N和B
function computer the N minus a and log of BN and I remind you this a N and B
of BN and I remind you this a N and B else we defined them when we computed
否则我们在计算变异分布时就定义了它们，因此
else we defined them when we computed the variational distributions so
the variational distributions so basically L of Q it's all kind of a
基本上是Q的L都是公式，所以你需要做的就是
basically L of Q it's all kind of a formula so what you need to do is as you
formula so what you need to do is as you update these lambdas and alphas and
更新两个正文中的这些lambda，alpha和beta，并
update these lambdas and alphas and betas in the two bodies and
betas in the two bodies and distributions you actually have to plot
您实际上必须将其分配出来-并扰乱
distributions you actually have to plot this out - and disturb that is
this out - and disturb that is monotonically increasing if it is not
如果不是，则单调增加
monotonically increasing if it is not either
either the calculation of the the distributions
分布的计算是错误的，或者基本上是您的计算
the calculation of the the distributions is wrong or basically your calculations
is wrong or basically your calculations of the lower bound is incorrect okay
下界的是不正确的
这是非常重要的，您必须在每个问题中都做到这一点
is wrong or basically your calculations of the lower bound is incorrect okay
this is very essential you have to do this in every problem
好吧，我会解决的，因为我们为单一高斯讨论了计算
well I'd solution since we talked about for the single Gaussian about computing
for the single Gaussian about computing the lower bound right to say that we
说我们已适当优化的下限权利，让我们讨论一下她
the lower bound right to say that we optimized properly let's discuss her a
optimized properly let's discuss her a bit rational influenced many variation
理性在模型的背景下影响了盒式任务的许多变化
bit rational influenced many variation of box missions in the context of model
of box missions in the context of model selection of a belief in in this case I
在这种情况下选择信念，我根本不是关于模型选择，而是
selection of a belief in in this case I am not at all about model selection but
am not at all about model selection but we spend a lot of times
我们在秋天花了很多时间在许多讲座上
we spend a lot of times lots of lectures on in the fall to
lots of lectures on in the fall to discuss about model selection so the
讨论有关模型选择的问题，所以这里的想法是您知道您可能有
discuss about model selection so the idea here is you know you may have
idea here is you know you may have different models that you label them
可以给它们贴上标签的不同型号，也许您可​​以放一些
different models that you label them with them all right maybe you put some
with them all right maybe you put some Flyers of this models and you have some
这个模型的传单，您还有一些约会，您想弄清楚什么是
Flyers of this models and you have some date and you want to figure out what is
date and you want to figure out what is the best model all right what's the best
最好的模型好了，什么是最好的模型，所以问题是
the best model all right what's the best model so the question is can you
model so the question is can you actually use variation optimization
实际使用变化优化变化我们有兴趣找到最佳的
actually use variation optimization variation our interest to find the best
variation our interest to find the best model so in principle what I'm asking is
模型，所以原则上我要问的是可能的
model so in principle what I'm asking is will be possible
will be possible let's say you start with some prior that
假设您先从此开始，然后根据您所说的具有说服力的格式
let's say you start with some prior that this given the telling formative you put
this given the telling formative you put the same probability in all the models
在所有模型中都具有相同的概率，您可以从数据a中计算齿轮吗？
the same probability in all the models can you calculate gears from data a
can you calculate gears from data a variation of posterior of M where m is a
M的后验变化，其中m是模型，所以让我们知道模型
variation of posterior of M where m is a model so let's have models you know
model so let's have models you know what's the best model right and we will
什么是最佳模型权，我们将在以下情况下做到这一点
what's the best model right and we will do this you know in the context of
do this you know in the context of regression I think possibly today all
回归我认为今天可能还可以，但我想做一些非常
regression I think possibly today all right but I wanted to do sort of a very
right but I wanted to do sort of a very feeble calculation to see the
微不足道的计算，看得出变分计算实际上是
feeble calculation to see the variational calculations can actually be
variational calculations can actually be used to compute the posterior of that
用来计算该问题的后验，所以基本上我们在这里看
used to compute the posterior of that okay so so basically we're looking here
okay so so basically we're looking here is if we have some data X right can we
如果我们有一些数据X可以计算出山的后部
is if we have some data X right can we calculate the posterior of the mountain
calculate the posterior of the mountain the beta example affirmative say it's
beta示例表示肯定，它的回归可能为负，等于1 / s
the beta example affirmative say it's regression may be negative equal to 1/s
regression may be negative equal to 1/s you use linear concepts maybe different
您使用线性概念，也许其他人使用二次函数模型
you use linear concepts maybe different person use quadratic functions model
person use quadratic functions model equal three cubic functions or maybe you
等于三个三次函数，或者您可能知道不止一个，就是使用一个基数
equal three cubic functions or maybe you know more than one is you use one basis
know more than one is you use one basis function or the to two basis functions
职能或以两个职能为基础的三个职能部门
function or the to two basis functions three based processes which man who does
three based processes which man who does the best all right but you have to sit
最好，但您必须坐下来以了解这些计算结果
the best all right but you have to sit for money how these calculations come in
for money how these calculations come in the context of this variational method
这种变分方法的上下文，所以我们将做一些简单的琐碎的事情
the context of this variational method so we'll do some simple trivial nothing
so we'll do some simple trivial nothing sophisticated yet so wanna do is let's
复杂，但我们想做的是，每个模型都有自己的本地
sophisticated yet so wanna do is let's say that every model has its own local
say that every model has its own local variables
变数
所以您知道，当我尝试定义后验的变化近似值时
say that every model has its own local variables
so you know so when I try to define a variation approximation of the posterior
所以您知道，当我尝试定义后验的变化近似值时
variation approximation of the posterior of znm I am gonna write it as follows
Znm的写法，如下所示：Z的国家分布
of znm I am gonna write it as follows somebody a tional distribution of Z
somebody a tional distribution of Z given M so this is an approximation the
给定M，所以这是超超高分模型的后验
given M so this is an approximation the posterior of the super hyper score model
posterior of the super hyper score model M times the posterior on the left
M乘以左边的后验，所以什么也没做，所以需要一些计算
M times the posterior on the left alright so nothing so some calculations
alright so nothing so some calculations here to see how this whole thing's come
在这里看到这整个事情如何走向其他人是近似的
here to see how this whole thing's come to the others are approximation to the
to the others are approximation to the low black we would without any
低矮的黑色，我们将无需对恐怖模式进行任何讨论，所以
low black we would without any discussion of model terror all right so
discussion of model terror all right so what I have done is I give the
我所做的是给下界的定义
what I have done is I give the definition of the lower bound
definition of the lower bound alright and then I suppose you remember
好吧，那么我想你记得关于
alright and then I suppose you remember what the expectation with respect to the
what the expectation with respect to the latent power also in this case the
在这种情况下，潜能也确实是CNN
latent power also in this case the latent variables really CNN they are
latent variables really CNN they are both unknowns
两个未知数都可以，我把它放在后面，这是我的
both unknowns okay and I put the posterior this is my
okay and I put the posterior this is my approximate posterior this is the
大概后验这是期望部分，然后我有日志
approximate posterior this is the expectation part and then I have the log
expectation part and then I have the log the joint look likelihood noticed a
关节的外观似乎注意到了我的蒸气有点活跃
the joint look likelihood noticed a little active with this my vapors
little active with this my vapors detects my ZN my model because I how
检测我的模型的ZN，因为我是如何做到这一点的，
detects my ZN my model because I how does that have put the motive to be and
does that have put the motive to be and I know this is basically about models
我知道这基本上是关于模型，然后是分母
I know this is basically about models okay and then of the denominator
okay and then of the denominator obviously have the same foreign
显然具有相同的外国发行额，因此您可以编写相同的
obviously have the same foreign distribution so you can write the same
distribution so you can write the same as before so here what I do is I write
和以前一样，在这里我要做的是给定ZN m的确切后置恐惧
as before so here what I do is I write the exact post fear of ZN m given the
the exact post fear of ZN m given the data times few effects and this like
数据乘以几个效果，这样就可以了，在最后一行中
data times few effects and this like that okay and and in this last line with
that okay and and in this last line with like this I take this P effects and I
像这样，我采取了这种P效果，并删除了它，因为它不依赖于
like this I take this P effects and I remove it out because doesn't depend on
remove it out because doesn't depend on M and D respectively what I get is this
我得到的M和D分别是这个好东西加上X和P的对数
M and D respectively what I get is this nice thing plus log of P of X and you
nice thing plus log of P of X and you probably might if you love of the
如果您对效果的热爱基本上是下限，可能会
probably might if you love of the effects is basically the lower bound
effects is basically the lower bound - this okay does this remind you
-这样做可以使您想起任何事情，但请记住我们
- this okay does this remind you anything what is remember the one we
anything what is remember the one we have the fundamental identity that the
具有对数似然不同的基本身份
have the fundamental identity that the log likelihood is different the lower
log likelihood is different the lower bound and Wiggins was there became of
绑定和Wiggins的尺寸变大了，唯一的区别是
bound and Wiggins was there became of dimensions the only difference here is
dimensions the only difference here is instead of a sphere of Z I have the
而不是ZI领域，证明CNN正确的解决方案已更改
instead of a sphere of Z I have the proof CNN right solution has changed
proof CNN right solution has changed okay very much imperative to tell you on
好吧，当务之急是告诉您如何为朋友计算
okay very much imperative to tell you on how you compute for your friends so
how you compute for your friends so let's see what we can do this so long
让我们看看我们能做到这一点这么久，这是说您可以走了
let's see what we can do this so long ado this is let's say you can maybe go
ado this is let's say you can maybe go in addition approximations on each model
此外，还可以估算每个模型的近似值
in addition approximations on each model and if you can then calculate
and if you can then calculate below the bar for its problem so L M is
在酒吧下面的问题，所以LM是长度较低的浴室，而我
below the bar for its problem so L M is the lower bathroom of the length and I
the lower bathroom of the length and I write it like that everybody agrees I
像每个人都同意这样写，我的意思是你可以在这里看到那是什么
write it like that everybody agrees I mean you can see here what is that is
mean you can see here what is that is the joint alive you could form on the
活着的关节，你可以在水平上形成，没有什么花哨的
the joint alive you could form on the level there's nothing fancy
level there's nothing fancy okay my conditioner to your embassy
好吧，我的护发素对你的大使馆是正确的，所以问题是一旦我有
okay my conditioner to your embassy right so the question is once I have
right so the question is once I have this can I come up with a novel lower
我基本上可以为我的整个问题提出一个新颖的下界
this can I come up with a novel lower bound basically for my whole problem for
bound basically for my whole problem for mothers have been integrate doubt so
母亲们一直在怀疑，所以让我们看看计算结果如何
mothers have been integrate doubt so let's see how the calculation looks like
let's see how the calculation looks like it's actually very interesting in Sabra
在Sabra中，这实际上非常有趣，这是我们开始之前就可以做的
it's actually very interesting in Sabra this is what we started before all right
this is what we started before all right this is having a variation of
这是分布模型和所有疾病的变化
this is having a variation of distribution models and all disease for
distribution models and all disease for each model so what I do is I write the
每个模型，所以我要做的是在这里写下缺少它的实际连接
each model so what I do is I write the actual join of lack of it here as the
actual join of lack of it here as the probability of Z and X given M plus the
给定M加上Z和X的概率加上它们的先验，然后在
probability of Z and X given M plus the prior of them all right and then on the
prior of them all right and then on the denominator I have minus log of Q of Z M
分母我有减去ZM的Q的对数，如果您还好
denominator I have minus log of Q of Z M and if you alright
and if you alright I let's see I shake here I'm going to
我看我在这里摇晃，我要把其中两个放好
I let's see I shake here I'm going to put two of them outside okay
put two of them outside okay so cute n goes to the whole thing so I'm
很可爱，n遍及整个事情，所以我要把em的Q放到外面，所以我有P
so cute n goes to the whole thing so I'm going to put Q of em outside so I have P
going to put Q of em outside so I have P of M and then of p.m. nice Ln of QM nice
的M，然后是pm的，QM的Ln很好，我显然有M的总和。
of M and then of p.m. nice Ln of QM nice I have obviously the summation of M will
I have obviously the summation of M will been outside then I have a summation on
在外面，那么我对Z求和，这取决于G，所以
been outside then I have a summation on Z and this thing right depends on G so
Z and this thing right depends on G so I'm going to have cube CM and then of P
我要有立方体CM，然后是Z逗号X的P立方体，给我们，
I'm going to have cube CM and then of P of Z comma X given them and we have this
of Z comma X given them and we have this curve as well will you agree the fiscal
曲线也一样，您会同意财政认为这确实会吸引神吗
curve as well will you agree the fiscal think it is really ll compelling to God
think it is really ll compelling to God is it
是对吗，对不起，我在写
is it it is right all right sorry I'm writing
it is right all right sorry I'm writing this whole thing then qfm love of
这整个事情，然后qfm热爱戏剧-热爱儿童，我应该
this whole thing then qfm love of theater - love of children and I should
theater - love of children and I should have LM so if I did this love of it -
有LM，所以，如果我热爱它-11对没什么特别的
have LM so if I did this love of it - the 11 right nothing spectacular there's
the 11 right nothing spectacular there's a reason for this I arrived it like that
我之所以这样来的原因是因为这样我就可以写整个
a reason for this I arrived it like that because then I can write this whole the
because then I can write this whole the overall lower bound I can write this
总体下限，我可以将这条船的ln pfm乘以C到LM / q /
overall lower bound I can write this ship m ln of pfm times C to the LM / q /
ship m ln of pfm times C to the LM / q / and so look at this nice now the
所以现在看一下下界的关系，然后告诉我
and so look at this nice now the relation of the lower bounds and tell me
relation of the lower bounds and tell me what is this nice quantity now that that
现在，按定义提醒您的好数量是多少
what is this nice quantity now that that remind you by definition
来吧，我Sakura Sakura威尼斯是一回事
come on I Sakura Sakura Venice is something
I Sakura Sakura Venice is something there it doesn't have to remind you this
那里不必提醒您这个问题，今天是我们所拥有的
there it doesn't have to remind you this question today was something we have
question today was something we have mentioned maybe something would have not
提到也许没有提及，但是根据定义这是什么
mentioned maybe something would have not mentioned but what is this by definition
工作
the work
我在这里，谢谢您记住噪声过滤，这是一个非线性过滤
I'm here thank you remember noise filtering and it's a nonlinear filtering
filtering and it's a nonlinear filtering all right so what is that entity is -
好吧，那个实体是什么-这个词
all right so what is that entity is - the word
现在看起来像是一个期望，但是对什么是更好的定义
now it looks like an expectation but there is a better definition of what is
there is a better definition of what is this is - I gave you half of the story -
这是-我给你讲了一半的故事-是因为Q和P之间的KL差异
this is - I gave you half of the story - out of the KL divergence between Q and P
out of the KL divergence between Q and P of 10 times e to the 11 all right so the
是11的10倍e的倍数，所以目标是使总体
of 10 times e to the 11 all right so the objective is to maximize the overall
objective is to maximize the overall lower bound then you have to minimize
下界，那么你必须最小化
这，我们知道确切的答案，当qfm等于
objective is to maximize the overall lower bound then you have to minimize
this and we know the exact answer right this will be optimised when qfm equal to
这，我们知道确切的答案，当qfm等于
this will be optimised when qfm equal to PM e to the LM where the ram is equal
PM e到LM等于ram的LM，所以现在真的是第一次
PM e to the LM where the ram is equal like that so really now for the first
like that so really now for the first time you no need to slide you have seen
当您无需滑动时，您已经看到模型的后验
time you no need to slide you have seen a variational posterior of a model in
a variational posterior of a model in two slides okay so you can I mean this
两张幻灯片都可以，所以我可以说，如果您想
two slides okay so you can I mean this can be extremely useful if you want to
can be extremely useful if you want to do model selection in regression
在回归分类中选择模型只是提及其中
do model selection in regression classification just mention it which
classification just mention it which model does the best alright so this
模型做得最好，所以这给了你一个近似值
model does the best alright so this gives you an approximation give it the
gives you an approximation give it the data of the posterior over models and if
模型的后验数据，如果您为模型1 2和3绘制此图，则您
data of the posterior over models and if you plot this for model 1 2 &amp; 3 etc you
you plot this for model 1 2 &amp; 3 etc you know you will eventually be able to do
知道您最终将能够进行模型选择，弄清楚这是什么
know you will eventually be able to do model selection figure out what's the
model selection figure out what's the best model that interprets the data okay
解释数据的最佳模型还可以，因此使用
best model that interprets the data okay so this is a very nice calculation using
so this is a very nice calculation using variational methods of expense basically
费用变动法基本上是这个用于分配的概念
variational methods of expense basically this concept for computing distribution
this concept for computing distribution of related variables now computing
的相关变量现在计算潜在变量的分布，并且
of related variables now computing distributions over latent variables and
distributions over latent variables and models
型号很好，非常好
models alright so very nice
1990年的草食，所以他们决定这个，如果有新的
so
the 1990 pastula so they decide on this actually where I can if there is a new
1990年的草食，所以他们决定这个，如果有新的
actually where I can if there is a new tactic that's a little bit more
这种策略比即将来临的主题要复杂一点，但是
tactic that's a little bit more complicated than the topics to come but
complicated than the topics to come but because I need somehow put them together
因为我需要以某种方式将它们放在一起让我让它正确完成并尝试
because I need somehow put them together let me let me finish it up right and try
let me let me finish it up right and try to do our best to understand it again
尽我们最大的努力再次理解它，这将是汤姆治安官，有点
to do our best to understand it again this will be by Sheriff Tom it's a bit
this will be by Sheriff Tom it's a bit more difficult than some of the problems
比接下来将要看到的一些问题更困难，但让我们滚蛋
more difficult than some of the problems we will see next but let's get get out
we will see next but let's get get out of the way okay well first what the
首先，通心粉是关于什么的，所以您在这里看到的是
of the way okay well first what the macaronis is about so what you see here
macaronis is about so what you see here is a model where you know I mean it
是一个模型，您知道我的意思是在先前的讲座中下雪了
is a model where you know I mean it snows here in earlier lectures the
snows here in earlier lectures the difference from what we discussed in
与我们在hmm的大多数演示中讨论的内容不同的是
difference from what we discussed in most of the presentations from hmm is
most of the presentations from hmm is but we have multiple chains but they're
但是我们有多个链条，但是它们被链接在一起并且被链接在一起
but we have multiple chains but they're linked together and they're linked
linked together and they're linked together as you can see because the
如您所见，因为每次的观察都取决于
together as you can see because the observations of every time dependent on
observations of every time dependent on the state of all the change okay so if
所有更改的状态都可以，因此，如果您尝试实际发送消息，并且您
the state of all the change okay so if you try to actually messaging and you
you try to actually messaging and you know the cell phone data messages to do
知道手机数据报文是这样做的，因为链条耦合好了
know the cell phone data messages to do it because the chains are coupled okay
it because the chains are coupled okay the list would be a serious limitation
该列表将严重限制我们在上下文中学到的东西
the list would be a serious limitation of the things we learned in the context
of the things we learned in the context of what's called proctorial hidden
所谓的检控隐马尔可夫模型好了，那我就不
of what's called proctorial hidden Markov models okay so then I don't
Markov models okay so then I don't highlight basically today it can somehow
今天基本上强调它可以从某种程度上减少一些想法
highlight basically today it can somehow reduce some ideas from variational
reduce some ideas from variational method and the star approximation of the
方法和这个阶段的后验星近似
method and the star approximation of the posterior of this stage of the different
posterior of this stage of the different change in a way that somehow uncouples
以某种方式将它们解耦的方式进行更改
change in a way that somehow uncouples them in
them in in a manner that somehow allow us to use
以某种方式使我们能够利用我的第一个大师传播
in a manner that somehow allow us to use forward my first Masters propagation the
forward my first Masters propagation the way we have seen it for one chain in the
我们过去在一个链条上看到它的方式，或者您知道独立文本的方式，所以
way we have seen it for one chain in the past or you know for independent text so
past or you know for independent text so let's determine deed to see if Malaysia
让我们确定行动，看看马来西亚梅蒂斯是否真的对此有任何看法
let's determine deed to see if Malaysia Metis actually are any views on this
Metis actually are any views on this problem
问题，我的意思是我们将看到违反武器
problem I mean violation weapons we will see
I mean violation weapons we will see there of use for everything okay the
可以使用所有东西，可以先使用所有东西的近似方法
there of use for everything okay the approximate method for everything first
approximate method for everything first example if you can think here my
例如，如果您可以认为我的课程提纲真的很好，那就是
example if you can think here my syllabus is really act alright this is
syllabus is really act alright this is the unknown states the data why you can
未知状态说明数据，为什么您可以在这里坚持很多，所以如果加入
the unknown states the data why you can stick here much so if the joining
stick here much so if the joining likelihood is basically my transition
可能性基本上是我从t减去一二三的转换模型
likelihood is basically my transition model from t minus one two three okay
model from t minus one two three okay and the observation model okay and you
观察模型还可以，您会注意到这里有一个副本，我是
and the observation model okay and you notice there is a copy here and I'm
notice there is a copy here and I'm gonna show you here explicitly because
要在这里明确地告诉你，因为为什么P取决于所有这些轴
gonna show you here explicitly because why P depends on the axis of all these
why P depends on the axis of all these state X M alright and this the profit
声明XM好吧，这简让简的利润我的意思是约翰喜欢
state X M alright and this the profit the Jane looked like I mean John like
the Jane looked like I mean John like liquids a product over the change and
在变更后为产品浇灌液体，并且在所有情况下都能正常运转，因此
liquids a product over the change and all the time instances teeth okay so the
all the time instances teeth okay so the definition is very very similar to what
定义与我们从确切的日志中看到的非常相似
definition is very very similar to what we have seen from the exact logs on a
we have seen from the exact logs on a log likelihood that we have seen the
我们已经看到陷阱的对数可能性，所以我们为
log likelihood that we have seen the trap so a we give a for the
trap so a we give a for the transition matrix we have some
过渡矩阵，我们对初始空间有一些概率
transition matrix we have some probabilities for the initial space
probabilities for the initial space which is better from what we have done
这比我们几年前所做的更好，但是有一个很好的指数
which is better from what we have done before years but there is an index well
before years but there is an index well there is a named exam because this
有一个命名考试，因为这种过渡概率和初始
there is a named exam because this transition probabilities and initial
transition probabilities and initial probabilities have to refer to its chain
概率必须参考从k 1到M的链K，所以可能性
probabilities have to refer to its chain K from k 1 to M okay so the likelihood
K from k 1 to M okay so the likelihood model this is departure from what we
模型，这与我们在hmm演示中所做的不同
model this is departure from what we have done in the hmm presentations it is
have done in the hmm presentations it is now the moon is defined to be estimation
现在，月亮被定义为对月球的估计
now the moon is defined to be estimation of the
of the raishin basically a linear weighted sum
raishin基本上是此时状态与状态的线性加权和
raishin basically a linear weighted sum of the states at this time and the
of the states at this time and the coefficients here we take them to be
系数在这里我们以开始就可以给出，所以均值是
coefficients here we take them to be given to start with okay so the mean is
given to start with okay so the mean is given some linear interpolation between
给定X的所有变化之间的线性插值
given some linear interpolation between the values of X's all the change
the values of X's all the change mm remember me from little n equal to R
我记得从小等于R到大写M的名字，所以没关系，
mm remember me from little n equal to R to capital M okay so this is alright and
to capital M okay so this is alright and it's computationally very difficult to
由于这个等式，因此在计算上很难使用
it's computationally very difficult to work with because of this equation so
work with because of this equation so this equation constraint so you won't be
这个方程式约束，所以您将无法知道自己是否期望
this equation constraint so you won't be able you know if you do expectation
able you know if you do expectation maximization for example and compute the
例如最大化并计算您将无法获得的足够统计量
maximization for example and compute the sufficient statistic you won't be able
sufficient statistic you won't be able to use for the backward message passing
用于后向消息传递，因为这些消息是耦合的，所以它
to use for the backward message passing because these messages are coupled so it
because these messages are coupled so it will be computationally very big okay so
在计算上会很好，所以我认为确切的后验
will be computationally very big okay so I am I think the exact posterior
I am I think the exact posterior basically using the exact joint local
基本上使用确切的联合本地文章，因此基本上将其扩展为
basically using the exact joint local article so expanding it basically this
article so expanding it basically this is the name of the probability value
是上一张幻灯片中显示的概率值的名称，因此
is the name of the probability value shown in the previous slide so this
shown in the previous slide so this comes from the data likelihood that's
来自于耦合的数据可能性还可以，它是高斯
comes from the data likelihood that's for the coupling is okay it's a Gaussian
for the coupling is okay it's a Gaussian and we have thinking lungs so this
我们在想肺，所以这里的向量是
and we have thinking lungs so this vector here is the log of the
vector here is the log of the probabilities of the initial States for
初始国家对其链m的概率，这是
probabilities of the initial States for its chain m and this is the launch of
its chain m and this is the launch of the transition probabilities for each
每个州的转移概率，实际上几乎没有
the transition probabilities for each state and there is really nothing near
state and there is really nothing near from what we discussed with hmm except
根据我们与hmm讨论的内容，除了现在我拥有的不是
from what we discussed with hmm except the fact now that I have instead of
the fact now that I have instead of having one chain I have a summation of
有一个链，我对所有变化的每个状态及其求和求和
having one chain I have a summation of each state of all the change with their
each state of all the change with their own profit initial probabilities and in
自己的利润初始概率，并且在过渡中具有另一个求和
own profit initial probabilities and in the transitions have another summation
the transitions have another summation then for all the transition
那么对于所有的转移概率，所以我们需要找到
then for all the transition probabilities right so we need to find
probabilities right so we need to find some way to
一些方法来近似推断来解决这个问题
some way to just approximate inference to solve this
just approximate inference to solve this problem okay and the idea is the
问题好了，想法是像世界是近似的差异
problem okay and the idea is the difference like the world is approximate
difference like the world is approximate so miss can you have to use your
所以小姐，您是否可以使用您的直觉，或者您说我要尝试
so miss can you have to use your intuition or you say I'm gonna try
intuition or you say I'm gonna try something that looks like that and let's
看起来像这样的东西，让我们希望最好
something that looks like that and let's hope for the best
hope for the best all right so the situation we will
好的，所以我们将要讨论的情况是一个近似值
all right so the situation we will discuss is an approximation that will
discuss is an approximation that will decouple the change okay so somehow we
解耦变更好吧，所以我们以某种方式将它们解耦，这样我们就可以成为
decouple the change okay so somehow we decouple them so that way we can become
decouple them so that way we can become messages back and forth basically change
现在，来回消息基本上独立地更改为其中的几个
messages back and forth basically change independently now to the couple of them
independently now to the couple of them let me just tell you what the idea is
让我告诉你这个主意显然是什么，所以如果我们尝试近似
let me just tell you what the idea is obviously so if we try to approximate
obviously so if we try to approximate them it's independent can you imagine in
它们是独立的，您能在保持近似的情况下想象吗
them it's independent can you imagine in the context of maintained approximations
the context of maintained approximations something we need to do to get rid of
我们需要做的一些事情来摆脱这个术语，这是
something we need to do to get rid of this term here this is the evidence for
this term here this is the evidence for typos everything together
错别字，所有内容都可以让您想起某种您知道的东西
typos everything together can you think of some sort of you know
can you think of some sort of you know idea with a backward message passing on
一个向后消息传递相同的想法，但我们将能够
idea with a backward message passing on its same but we're going to be able to
its same but we're going to be able to account mission is I mean it's insane
帐户任务是我的意思是疯狂，但实际上
account mission is I mean it's insane does really does but in the average
does really does but in the average sentence to detect so we need to abuse
句子来检测，所以我们需要滥用一些证据不容错过的概念
sentence to detect so we need to abuse some concept of evidenced not miss
some concept of evidenced not miss evidence but some local evidence that is
证据，但在每个出现的链条中都引入了一些当地证据
evidence but some local evidence that is introduced in every chain that comes
introduced in every chain that comes from the fact of all the change make
从所有变化的事实来看是有道理的
from the fact of all the change make sense
sense all right so we're gonna run them
好的，所以我们要独立运行它们，但是必须有一些
all right so we're gonna run them independently but there must be some
independently but there must be some things that influences would say train
有影响力的事情会说训练一个，因为这种变化在某些方面
things that influences would say train one because this change had in some
one because this change had in some state okay so here right actually one of
声明好吧，所以实际上这里是您在这些问题上需要的问题之一
state okay so here right actually one of the questions you need on the on those
the questions you need on the on those three lines so this evidence at this
三行，所以这个证据在这个时候我称之为c PM k好，时间T
three lines so this evidence at this time I call it c PM k alright and time T
time I call it c PM k alright and time T it refers to chain M okay and tell them
它指的是链M并告诉他们，因为监听hmm可以处于状态K
it refers to chain M okay and tell them because listen hmm can be in state K is
because listen hmm can be in state K is what stated this so tell us what is c TM
这么说是什么，所以告诉我们这里的c TM k试图做什么
what stated this so tell us what is c TM k trying to do in this equation here
没有证据表明没有发布会从图片中消失
there's no evidence there's no the release will disappear from the picture
release will disappear from the picture there's no evidence or anything like
没有证据或类似的东西
there's no evidence or anything like that
that right when the evidence comes from this
正确，当证据来自此，因此我们将进行此测试确实是
right when the evidence comes from this exists so we'll do this test really are
exists so we'll do this test really are trying to accomplish the way that you
试图完成您在幻灯片上看到它们的方式
trying to accomplish the way that you see them on the slide
因此，例如，您知道这是从时间t开始的火车em的过渡
so for example you know this is a transition for train em from time t
transition for train em from time t minus 1 t 2 t but you notice I'm
负1吨2吨，但您注意到我在Shion上对其进行了调节
minus 1 t 2 t but you notice I'm conditioning it on Shion
所以注册，我们不是说这个人讨论过这个词，不是意思
so register we don't mean a word discussed this man so not meaning are
discussed this man so not meaning are you going to attach to this chaps
你会喜欢这个家伙
举办了一个研讨会，我很高兴他们必须完成他们，我们不知道他们在哪里
discussed this man so not meaning are you going to attach to this chaps
hosted a seminar I was well they have to complete them we have no idea where they
举办了一个研讨会，我很高兴他们必须完成他们，我们不知道他们在哪里
complete them we have no idea where they are but we're trying to mimic something
是，但是我们正在尝试模仿某些东西，无论我们是否正在尝试模仿这里的
are but we're trying to mimic something whether we're trying to mimic here a
高斯混合体
mixture of gaussians
我记得这里的这种黏土是因为我已经将它们解锁
I remember like this this clay thing here is because I have unchain them
对，所以这是唯一可以让我介绍当地人的地方
right so this is the only place that will allow me to introduce local
will allow me to introduce local evidence in the model all right so in
模型中的证据还可以，因此从本质上讲消除了所有这些
evidence in the model all right so in essence getting rid of all of these
essence getting rid of all of these things right we're going to do a
正确的事情，我们将做一个变化近似消除
things right we're going to do a variation approximation getting rid of
variation approximation getting rid of this cutting here all right so this
这个切口在这里好吧，所以这将是一个身体痣，占
this cutting here all right so this would be a body mole that accounts for
would be a body mole that accounts for the effect of all the other change from
来自中国的所有其他变化的影响，好吧，我们不知道K的G
the effect of all the other change from China okay we have no idea what G of K
China okay we have no idea what G of K is so we're gonna have to go in
是这样，我们将不得不进行计算，或者您知道已编写
is so we're gonna have to go in computation or you know is written
computation or you know is written basically like this okay this is for the
基本上是这样，这是针对初始状态的，所以我们知道是针对每个状态的
basically like this okay this is for the initial state so as we know is for every
initial state so as we know is for every chain from M 1 to M so this is for the
从M 1到M的链条，所以这是他们每趟火车的初始状态，
chain from M 1 to M so this is for the initial state in every train them and
initial state in every train them and this is for the for each type for each
这是针对每个链M的每种类型，从t减1到
this is for the for each type for each chain M the transition from t minus 1 to
chain M the transition from t minus 1 to t ok this is thunder what is different
好的，这是雷声这里不同的是，我们的条件是这些
t ok this is thunder what is different here is that we conditions is these
here is that we conditions is these things of local evidence 3 okay and the
地方证据的事3还可以，并且定义了两个变体
things of local evidence 3 okay and the definition of the two variation
definition of the two variation distributions is what you see here okay
分布就是您在这里看到的，好吧，这与之前的情况相同
distributions is what you see here okay this is the same as before this is the
this is the same as before this is the same as before this is now we plug it in
与以前一样，现在我们将其插入以帮助说明主要工艺
same as before this is now we plug it in helping to account for the main craft if
helping to account for the main craft if you like or probably other change from
您喜欢它的连锁店可能还有其他变化
you like or probably other change from its chain em alright
所以你知道当你基本计算时，你看起来像
so the you know when you calculate basically you take the joint look like
basically you take the joint look like they could do the variation
他们可以做变化近似可以相信
they could do the variation approximation can believe that in a
approximation can believe that in a gives form into some some energy EQ and
将形式转化为一些能量EQ，并且该能量基本上具有极高的
gives form into some some energy EQ and this energy basically has an extremely
this energy basically has an extremely simple fall alright so obviously you are
简单的跌倒好吧，所以很明显，你会变得越来越长
simple fall alright so obviously you are going to get you're going to get long
going to get you're going to get long survey and long supply so this carrying
调查和长期供应，因此，该携带实体基本上是这个日志，还可以
survey and long supply so this carrying entities are basically the this log okay
entities are basically the this log okay so let's add all the terms come where is
因此，让我们添加所有术语吧，让这个Pam来自何先生。什么
so let's add all the terms come where is this Pam coming from let's have mr. what
this Pam coming from let's have mr. what is this term coming from
这个名词来自
这段时间是什么问题
this Pam coming from let's have mr. what is this term coming from
what is this time can be problem
我的意思是我们拥有的就是我们正在寻找的东西，而我正在记录日志
I mean we have this is what we're looking right and I'm taking logs what
looking right and I'm taking logs what them here will give me the stuff I
他们在这里会给我我包含游戏光盘学院的东西，
them here will give me the stuff I contain the game discs Academy is the
contain the game discs Academy is the number of districts II support that idea
第二区的许多人支持这个想法，而这个想法将来自于此，
number of districts II support that idea that will come from there from this and
that will come from there from this and there
那里
当您认为自己的病好后，这个术语就来自这个术语，这个术语将是
that will come from there from this and there
when you take your sis okay so this term comes from this term this term will be
当您认为自己的病好后，这个术语就来自这个术语，这个术语将是
comes from this term this term will be coming from latter
来自后者好吧，这个弯曲的区域是
coming from latter okay well this curvy area is the log of
okay well this curvy area is the log of this a this term here will come when you
当您记录日志或访问Lister时，这一个术语将在这里出现
this a this term here will come when you take logs or come Lister and the
take logs or come Lister and the incorporation of the loads from Lister
来自Lister的负载的合并已在求和中说明
incorporation of the loads from Lister is accounted already in the summation
is accounted already in the summation here starting from T equal to one
这里从T开始等于一个好的近似值右和变化
here starting from T equal to one okay approximation right and the change
okay approximation right and the change is there anything that is explicit that
是否有任何明显的东西，这取决于其他所有东西
is there anything that is explicit that this same depends on all the other
this same depends on all the other change and I remind you what coupling is
变化，我提醒您，接下来的耦合是什么耦合的，所以
change and I remind you what coupling is coupling at the following movin up so
coupling at the following movin up so the action for scalar is e to the minus
标量的作用是e减C和E好，您可以看到所有
the action for scalar is e to the minus C and E alright you can see all the
C and E alright you can see all the stage couple together okay alright so
舞台上的情侣在一起，好吧，所以您需要做的是
stage couple together okay alright so what you need to do is so we have the
what you need to do is so we have the actual energy and the action per student
实际能量和每个学生的动作，但我们不会以此为近似
actual energy and the action per student but we won't approximate it with this
but we won't approximate it with this and actively what you need to do is you
积极地需要做的是形成Q之间的KL距离
and actively what you need to do is you need to form the KL distance between Q
need to form the KL distance between Q and P and minimize the vehicle distance
和P，并根据我的长变量将车辆距离最小化
and P and minimize the vehicle distance with respect to what a long variable I'm
with respect to what a long variable I'm going to show you that the transition
向您展示过渡概率和初始概率
going to show you that the transition probabilities and initial probabilities
probabilities and initial probabilities are known so the only unknown on this
是已知的，所以在这个问题上唯一未知的将会很好，所以在这个
are known so the only unknown on this problem is going to be well so in this
problem is going to be well so in this model that is going to be beyond y'know
将会超越你所知的模型
事实-再次访问将是
problem is going to be well so in this model that is going to be beyond y'know
the truth - and again access will be the the
事实-再次访问将是
- and again access will be the the events and approximation of the local
事件和近似的当地证据来训练他们
events and approximation of the local evidence coming to train em from
evidence coming to train em from whatever checked so that's the only
不管检查什么，这是唯一未知的行，我们要修剪
whatever checked so that's the only unknown alright we're gonna trim the
unknown alright we're gonna trim the parameters B being a there are unit for
参数B为a
parameters B being a there are unit for simplicity minimization between the
simplicity minimization between the exact P and Q and you do the algebra I
精确的P和Q，然后您做代数我强烈建议您这样做
exact P and Q and you do the algebra I strongly recommend that you do it
strongly recommend that you do it because I did it and it may have some
因为我做到了，而且可能会有一些错别字，所以如果您这样做
because I did it and it may have some typos maybe not okay so if you do this
typos maybe not okay so if you do this and you do it carefully it comes out
而您仔细地做，结果表明您需要一个非常简单的
and you do it carefully it comes out that you need an extremely simple
that you need an extremely simple formula that they obeyed we also have
他们服从的公式我们也删除了状态K
formula that they obeyed we also have removed state K the update of this
removed state K the update of this record to see is this exponential of
可以看到的记录是此WM指标的这一指数值得记住
record to see is this exponential of this WM metrics that comes to remember
this WM metrics that comes to remember in the likelihoods and the covariance
在可能性和协方差减去一，这是证据
in the likelihoods and the covariance minus one and this is the evidence the
minus one and this is the evidence the data that is written like that okay and
这样写的数据可以
data that is written like that okay and this
this vente is is a vector that is formed
vente是基本上通过取对角线形成的向量
vente is is a vector that is formed basically by taking the diagonal
basically by taking the diagonal elements of this matrix the calculation
此矩阵的元素对于无限的计算是完美的，但是您
elements of this matrix the calculation is perfect for an infinitely but you
is perfect for an infinitely but you know there is really nothing else except
知道除了您必须计算
know there is really nothing else except you know that you have to calculate the
you know that you have to calculate the derivatives of the partition functions
归一化因子的分区函数的导数
derivatives of the partition functions of the normalization factors with
of the normalization factors with respect to sis so that's sort of the
对sis的尊重，所以这是唯一棘手的部分
respect to sis so that's sort of the only tricky part
only tricky part you cannot allow basically you to work
您基本上不能允许您使用未规范化的Q和P
you cannot allow basically you to work with Q and P that are not normalized so
with Q and P that are not normalized so you need to normalize them and that's
您需要对其进行规范化，这就是为什么要获得这些zq和锁的原因
you need to normalize them and that's why you get these locks of zq and locks
why you get these locks of zq and locks of Z but apart from that the rest is
的Z，但除此之外，其余只是历史，这是非常简单的
of Z but apart from that the rest is just history this is a very simple
just history this is a very simple formula all right and in other
好吧，在其他情况下，我会请你
formula all right and in other circumstances I will have asked you to
circumstances I will have asked you to write a little computer program to
编写一些计算机程序进行实际更改以检查此投资组合
write a little computer program to actually change to check this portfolio
actually change to check this portfolio key the Markov model
真正有效的马尔可夫模型的关键
key the Markov model it really works it really works
it really works it really works eben we're here has lots of intuition
eben我们在这里有很多直觉，他们在我们解耦
eben we're here has lots of intuition they're on the way we decouple the
they're on the way we decouple the evidence is that you worked quite well
有证据表明，您的工作还不错，如果再考虑一下，
evidence is that you worked quite well okay and again if you think about it the
okay and again if you think about it the only things you have to do is a simple
只需要做一个简单的更新公式即可，剩下的就是
only things you have to do is a simple update formula okay and the rest is
update formula okay and the rest is basically you know the rest is basically
基本上你知道剩下的基本上就是要做向前和向后的混乱
basically you know the rest is basically have to do a forward and backward mess
have to do a forward and backward mess the propagation the way we have done
一链和隐马尔可夫的传播方式
the propagation the way we have done earlier with one chain and hidden Markov
earlier with one chain and hidden Markov model
模型
我只有十分钟，对不起，基本上我只能开始一些事情，所以
earlier with one chain and hidden Markov model
I only have ten minutes sorry basically I can only I can only start something so
我只有十分钟，对不起，基本上我只能开始一些事情，所以
I can only I can only start something so we need I'm going to go to a slightly
我们需要针对那些
we need I'm going to go to a slightly different topic for those that are
different topic for those that are familiar with regression
熟悉回归
显然所有这些都将发布在网站上，所以让我让我向您展示
different topic for those that are familiar with regression
obviously all of this will be posted on the website so let me let me show you
显然所有这些都将发布在网站上，所以让我让我向您展示
the website so let me let me show you and maybe we can actually finish it in
如果我们可以线性的话，也许我们可以在10分钟内完成它
and maybe we can actually finish it in 10 minutes if we can be linear
10 minutes if we can be linear regression using okay now again I am I'm
再次使用回归，现在我将要谈论回归
regression using okay now again I am I'm going to be talking about regression
going to be talking about regression assuming everybody in the audience knows
假设听众中的每个人都知道回归
assuming everybody in the audience knows with regression
with regression okay here's some basis functions here a
好的，这里有一些基本函数，这里是线性回归模型，因此您可以考虑
okay here's some basis functions here a linear regression model so you can think
linear regression model so you can think that the response of the system that
您在此处指示的系统的响应让我
that the response of the system that you've indicated here with is let me
you've indicated here with is let me respond some with regular basis
使用定期计算的函数进行响应，您可以在任何时候进行计算
respond some with regular basis functions that you can calculate at any
functions that you can calculate at any point X plus some noise the defined here
X点加上一些噪声，这些噪声是由精度数据在这里定义的，所以基本上我是
point X plus some noise the defined here by the precision data so basically I'm
by the precision data so basically I'm taking that the likelihood of data is a
认为数据的可能性是其授权的成千上万的乘积
taking that the likelihood of data is a product of thousands it's authorized
product of thousands it's authorized over the iid day okay so a standard okay
在开斋节那天还可以，所以通常情况下，您在贝叶斯（Bayesian）所做的一切都很好
over the iid day okay so a standard okay usually what you do in in Bayesian
usually what you do in in Bayesian regression you're going to put some
回归你会给假人一些底漆在这里给一些
regression you're going to put some primer on the dummy here given some
primer on the dummy here given some precision alpha alright and then you put
精度alpha好吧，然后您将其放在优先位置上，我会看到
precision alpha alright and then you put some prior on that is taking I'll see
some prior on that is taking I'll see you at within this you can make this a
您可以在其中使它成为alpha的向量，并且您可以
you at within this you can make this a vector of alphas and you can do
vector of alphas and you can do relevance determination and all the this
相关性确定以及所有这些非常适合现代选择的东西
relevance determination and all the this very nice things for modern selection
very nice things for modern selection but right now there's only one alpha
但是现在只有一个Alpha好了
but right now there's only one alpha alright and
alright and and so what a bad review a laptop is the
因此，对笔记本电脑的不好评价是，先前的，令人恐惧的玩具和其他超级玩具
and so what a bad review a laptop is the prior and fearful toys and other hyper
prior and fearful toys and other hyper prior asking the posterior distribution
事先询问后验分布
解决方案，我们做的还不错，可以成为任何X的侦察兵，这一传统
prior and fearful toys and other hyper prior asking the posterior distribution
solution we have done it ok and become Scouts for any X so and this tradition
解决方案，我们做的还不错，可以成为任何X的侦察兵，这一传统
Scouts for any X so and this tradition where you know so basically an internet
如果您想到任何地方的生计，就基本上了解互联网
where you know so basically an internet if you think of the livelihood at any
if you think of the livelihood at any location X you know times the posterior
您知道的位置X乘以所有解的W的后验
location X you know times the posterior of W integrand of the solutions to all
of W integrand of the solutions to all of this but we pretend we don't know any
这个，但我们假装我们对此一无所知，我们真的很想看看
of this but we pretend we don't know any of this and we really want to see
of this and we really want to see Bayesian inference will actually is the
贝叶斯推断实际上是数据决定观察结果认为我是
Bayesian inference will actually is the data decide the observations think I'm
data decide the observations think I'm corresponding axis right so I only did
相应的轴正确，所以我今年才做，但请记住，这是
corresponding axis right so I only did that this year but remember this is
that this year but remember this is conditional on the axis as well okay
以轴为条件，好吧，弄乱轴并不重要
conditional on the axis as well okay it's not important to mess up the
it's not important to mess up the notation so the the likelihood is nice
记法，所以可能性很好，完全像那个，没有WI不知道是什么
notation so the the likelihood is nice exactly like that right no W I know what
exactly like that right no W I know what is the probability of T plus a prior or
T的概率加上给定的掌声的先验值或值，然后
is the probability of T plus a prior or value given applause all right and
value given applause all right and that's the probabilistic after model in
从简单的意义上讲，这就是概率模型，看起来像这样
that's the probabilistic after model in a simple sense looks like this okay a
a simple sense looks like this okay a plate rotation for the iid data and
iid数据的板旋转，并且基本上在此处W打开
plate rotation for the iid data and basically W open here
basically W open here remind me must be the high
提醒我，黑鬼一定是伽玛里面的高参数
remind me must be the high parameter coming inside of gamma
parameter coming inside of gamma distribution occasional vaccinations six
偶尔分发六天的疫苗，我们一直认为立方体W
distribution occasional vaccinations six days to go we've been assume that cube W
days to go we've been assume that cube W and alpha fertilize director whenever
和阿尔法施肥主任，只要你知道确切的
and alpha fertilize director whenever you have a knowledge of the exact
you have a knowledge of the exact solution we'll pretend we never read the
解决方案，我们假装我们从未读过书，所以您现在看到了，我们想要
solution we'll pretend we never read the books so you see now and we want
books so you see now and we want something that basically says that this
基本上可以说，这期WN总是W乘以P
something that basically says that this issue of WN always give W times P of
issue of WN always give W times P of alpha we have no idea what this
Alpha我们不知道这种分布应该如何
alpha we have no idea what this distribution should be okay
你显然要死了，如果你不能做到的话，你会把它杀死在那里很有趣
you clearly to death and you kill it there funny if you try to do it by can't
there funny if you try to do it by can't otherwise looking at it means nothing
否则看着它就什么也没有提醒我，所以Q的小说功能强大
otherwise looking at it means nothing I remind us so the novel by Q powerful
I remind us so the novel by Q powerful for example will be the expectation with
例如，将是对其他所有事物的期望
for example will be the expectation with respect to all the other very most so
respect to all the other very most so whether you are the variables here
你是否是这里的变量
这个问题有哪些未知数，所以您知道我们在这里计算出什么时
respect to all the other very most so whether you are the variables here
what are the unknowns in this problem so you know when we computed the here what
这个问题有哪些未知数，所以您知道我们在这里计算出什么时
you know when we computed the here what are the announces that we are not
是宣布我们可能还不是这样的期望或
are the announces that we are not probably still so the expectation or
probably still so the expectation or when I the join of market we're not
当我加入市场时，我们不会在这里抱期望
when I the join of market we're not going to be taking expectations here
going to be taking expectations here with respect to EE you okay so obviously
对于EE，您还可以，所以很明显，很长一段时间以来，
with respect to EE you okay so obviously was applied a long time there was a
was applied a long time there was a prior on da be given alpha and alpha
可以先获得阿尔法，而阿尔法不会进入液体中，所以您知道
prior on da be given alpha and alpha doesn't come in the liquid so you know
doesn't come in the liquid so you know constant so this is a gamma alright
常数，所以这是伽马，好吧，我们把它当作高斯假
constant so this is a gamma alright this we took it as a Gaussian sham
this we took it as a Gaussian sham taking the terms that depend on alpha
剩下依赖于alpha的术语，其余的我不在乎，
taking the terms that depend on alpha all right the rest I don't care and the
all right the rest I don't care and the expectation carries with respect to W
关于W的期望值可以，所以您认为分布
expectation carries with respect to W all right so the distribution you think
all right so the distribution you think you get for cute outfit here look I mean
你在这里得到了可爱的衣服，我的意思是，这就像一个小戏
you get for cute outfit here look I mean it was much like a little drama
it was much like a little drama distribution what do you think this is
您认为这是什么
优惠券的分布是什么
it was much like a little drama distribution what do you think this is
what's the distribution for coupons
如果只要伽玛分布随更新参数一起到达，因为
if as long as the gamma distribution arrived with updated parameters because
arrived with updated parameters because you can see never fast but here local
您可能看不到快，但这里是当地居民，所以您的零加M
you can see never fast but here local populace so you have a zero plus M over
populace so you have a zero plus M over 2 minus 1 so the first coefficient is a
2减去1，因此第一个系数为零，加上2上的10，并且BN等于
2 minus 1 so the first coefficient is a zero plus 10 over 2 and BN is equal to
zero plus 10 over 2 and BN is equal to that so T of a is a gamma distribution
所以a的T是伽马分布而不是putz
that so T of a is a gamma distribution not a putz you do the same thing with
not a putz you do the same thing with Dario the expectation now have to be
达里奥的期望现在必须尊重阿尔法，所以实际上并不令人惊讶
Dario the expectation now have to be respect to alpha so no surprise actually
respect to alpha so no surprise actually this distribution comes from be a
这个分布来自高斯，所以这是主要的
this distribution comes from be a Gaussian so that this is the main this
Gaussian so that this is the main this is the variance and no surprise by the
是方差，顺便说一句，每英尺的水都是alpha，这不足为奇
is the variance and no surprise by the way every foot of water is alpha you get
way every foot of water is alpha you get an expectation and the okay okay this is
期望和好吧好吧，这是让您知道的基础
an expectation and the okay okay this is making you know for basing the
making you know for basing the regression and the difference is there
回归，不同之处在于，现在有了表达式
regression and the difference is there was an alpha now we have the expression
好的，所以只有这样，我们需要检查一下，但是您会注意到
okay so this only having okay this we need to check it out but you notice the
need to check it out but you notice the coupling right to compute the
耦合权以计算alpha您的变化分布
coupling right to compute the distribution of variation of alpha you
distribution of variation of alpha you need to know the moment W of the
需要知道期望的时刻W，这意味着我现在想
need to know the moment W of the expectation that means I suppose now
expectation that means I suppose now here so you obviously have to couple the
在这里，所以您显然必须将两个方程式耦合好，好吧，所以
here so you obviously have to couple the two equations okay so alright so
two equations okay so alright so actually the results it says here from
实际上，这里所说的结果来自它们看起来完全一样的惊人之处
actually the results it says here from what amazing they look exactly the same
what amazing they look exactly the same reason as you get with expectation
期望最大化带来的原因
reason as you get with expectation maximization
maximization the only difference is basically if you
唯一的区别是，如果您使用alpha的期望值，可以
the only difference is basically if you use the expectation of alpha all right
use the expectation of alpha all right but we got those in the trivial manner
但我们以微不足道的方式获得了这些信息，从某种意义上讲，您知道它告诉您
but we got those in the trivial manner and in some sense you know it tells you
and in some sense you know it tells you that this techniques at the end of the
在一天结束时，这些技术是联系在一起的，我提醒您
that this techniques at the end of the day are linked together and I remind you
day are linked together and I remind you that when the most likely that
当最有可能的期望最大化是微不足道的
that when the most likely that expectation maximization is a trivial
expectation maximization is a trivial stuff case of the variational method
变数方法的正确案例，所以这很简单也就不足为奇了
stuff case of the variational method right so it's a simple not a surprise
right so it's a simple not a surprise that you get those results if you want
如果您想要预测分布，则可以得到这些结果，我们有一个
that you get those results if you want the predictive distribution we have one
the predictive distribution we have one minute to go basically that you need
分钟，基本上你需要这个，你需要整合很多东西
minute to go basically that you need this you need to integrate a lot to be
this you need to integrate a lot to be times the posterior and here because we
倍后验，在这里，因为如果您看不到，我们使用变分法
times the posterior and here because we use variational method if you don't see
use variational method if you don't see the exact posterior you put the
确切的后验，你把变分后验，这是
the exact posterior you put the variational posterior and this is the
variational posterior and this is the marginalization of the two gaussians
两个高斯的边缘化，这意味着这里是线性依赖性
marginalization of the two gaussians this mean here is a linear dependence
this mean here is a linear dependence from W so the solutions actually we have
从W开始，所以给出了我们实际上已经三遍看到的解决方案
from W so the solutions actually we have seen it in three times is given
seen it in three times is given analytically so basically that the mean
从理论上讲如此，以至于均值和方差就是方差权
analytically so basically that the mean and the variance the variance right is
and the variance the variance right is and again instead of PowerPoint you get
再一次，而不是PowerPoint，您会得到以下期望：
and again instead of PowerPoint you get the expectation of if you want to
the expectation of if you want to calculate the variable
计算这个男人来的可变惊喜
calculate the variable surprise surprise the man comes to have
surprise surprise the man comes to have a fantastic wonderful analytical form
奇妙的分析形式好吧，是的，如果您尝试将其应用于
a fantastic wonderful analytical form okay yes and if you try to apply this to
okay yes and if you try to apply this to a simple polynomial regression for
一个简单的多项式回归，例如，您问什么是
a simple polynomial regression for example you're asking what are the
example you're asking what are the polynomial M so I guess you know
多项式M，所以我想您显然知道可以使用任何最大值
polynomial M so I guess you know obviously you can use whatever maximize
obviously you can use whatever maximize the lower mountain in this case if you
在这种情况下，如果您执行此问题，则可以越下山越好
the lower mountain in this case if you do this problem you can all this Python
do this problem you can all this Python code you can see m equal to three
您可以看到m等于3的代码会使下限最大化
code you can see m equal to three maximizes the lower bound okay
maximizes the lower bound okay I warned you from us who study a
我从我们这里警告过您，他们研究了崩盘投资者回归分析，
I warned you from us who study a disintegration investor regression what
disintegration investor regression what she does with a single flaw but instead
她确实有一个缺陷，但不是拍打低矮的男人，而是
she does with a single flaw but instead of flapping the low block a man will be
of flapping the low block a man will be plot the model evidence because we can
绘制模型证据，因为我们可以在这里准确地假设是
plot the model evidence because we can exactly here the assumption is yes we
exactly here the assumption is yes we can calculate the mobile leg that's
可以计算出准确的移动行程，但是这种失败的想法非常
can calculate the mobile leg that's exactly but this idea of failure is very
exactly but this idea of failure is very powerful because in problems with the
之所以强大，是因为无法解决模型证据中的问题
powerful because in problems with the model evidence cannot be calculated you
model evidence cannot be calculated you can have many developed you okay so we
可以有很多发达的人吗，所以我们将在周四继续
can have many developed you okay so we will continue that on Thursday and
will continue that on Thursday and continuing become this topic then do
继续成为这个话题，然后用高斯混合和一些
continuing become this topic then do something with Gaussian mixture and some
something with Gaussian mixture and some other interesting aspects
其他有趣的方面